<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VFEPD_Glowstool.label>glowstool</VFEPD_Glowstool.label>
  <VFEPD_Glowstool.description>A fake small brown mushroom typically found in caves. It smells like an old, dirty rag pulled from the stomach of a rotting muffalo - but it tastes surprisingly good when cooked.</VFEPD_Glowstool.description>

  <VFEPD_Agarilux.label>agarilux</VFEPD_Agarilux.label>
  <VFEPD_Agarilux.description>A fake, enormous purple mushroom. Its size and glowing protrusions make this fungus beautiful to look at.</VFEPD_Agarilux.description>

  <VFEPD_Bryolux.label>bryolux</VFEPD_Bryolux.label>
  <VFEPD_Bryolux.description>A fake blue moss typically found in deep, dark caves. It is sticky, with tangled fibers, which slows anyone walking over it.</VFEPD_Bryolux.description>

  <VFEPD_Rose.label>rose</VFEPD_Rose.label>
  <VFEPD_Rose.description>A fake beautiful cultivated flower, the rose has been a symbol of love since Earth's ancient era.</VFEPD_Rose.description>

  <VFEPD_Daylily.label>daylily</VFEPD_Daylily.label>
  <VFEPD_Daylily.description>A cultivated fake flower with wide petals and a short lifespan. Daylilies are very beautiful, but must be replanted often.</VFEPD_Daylily.description>

  <VFEPD_Rice.label>rice plant</VFEPD_Rice.label>
  <VFEPD_Rice.description>A fake, short, fast-growing crop that yields small edible grains. Its great nutritional ouput and ease of cultivation has made it the economic core of many great civilizations. While rice grows quickly, it is sensitive to soil fertility and will not fare well in poor soil.</VFEPD_Rice.description>

  <VFEPD_Potato.label>potato plant</VFEPD_Potato.label>
  <VFEPD_Potato.description>A fake, highly nutritious tuber. Potatoes grow well even in somewhat poor soil, and form a delicious crispy outer coating when fried in oil.</VFEPD_Potato.description>

  <VFEPD_Corn.label>corn plant</VFEPD_Corn.label>
  <VFEPD_Corn.description>A fake tall grain plant which produces ears of soft, edible seeds. While corn takes a long time to grow, it yields lots of food compared to other crops. Harvested corn takes a long time to spoil.</VFEPD_Corn.description>

  <VFEPD_Strawberry.label>strawberry plant</VFEPD_Strawberry.label>
  <VFEPD_Strawberry.description>A fake, low bush-like plant that yields fragile but delicious strawberries. While it isn't quite as productive calorie-for-calorie as other crops, strawberries are delicious even when raw.</VFEPD_Strawberry.description>

  <VFEPD_Haygrass.label>haygrass</VFEPD_Haygrass.label>
  <VFEPD_Haygrass.description>A fake mixture of nutrient-rich grasses which yield large amounts of hay. Hay is edible for animals, but not humans.</VFEPD_Haygrass.description>

  <VFEPD_Cotton.label>cotton plant</VFEPD_Cotton.label>
  <VFEPD_Cotton.description>A fake mid-size crop that yields fine white cotton fibers. These are used to make cloth.</VFEPD_Cotton.description>

  <VFEPD_Devilstrand.label>devilstrand</VFEPD_Devilstrand.label>
  <VFEPD_Devilstrand.description>This fake fragile mushroom was genetically engineered to produce a silk net that is both difficult to tear and soft to the touch. While the mushroom takes a very long time to grow, only exotic ultra-tech fabrics outperform its devilstrand fibers.\n\nSome say it's called devilstrand because of its red color. Others think it owes its name to the greed it inspires in people.</VFEPD_Devilstrand.description>

  <VFEPD_Healroot.label>healroot</VFEPD_Healroot.label>
  <VFEPD_Healroot.description>A fake, slow-growing plant which yields herbal medicine when harvested. Sowing and harvesting healroot are both very labor-intensive tasks because of its delicate shoots.\n\nHealroot was selectively bred for centuries by settlers. It is sometimes also called "healer's hand" by tribespeople - a nickname it owes to its five major medicinal virtues.</VFEPD_Healroot.description>

  <VFEPD_Hops.label>hop plant</VFEPD_Hops.label>
  <VFEPD_Hops.description>A fake flowering crop that yields hops, an essential ingredient in beer.</VFEPD_Hops.description>

  <VFEPD_Smokeleaf.label>smokeleaf plant</VFEPD_Smokeleaf.label>
  <VFEPD_Smokeleaf.description>A fake leafy crop grown for the psychological effects of chemicals in its leaves. Smokeleaf leaves can be prepared into joints at the crafting spot. Smokeleaf makes a user feel relaxed, but reduces motivation, and can be addictive.</VFEPD_Smokeleaf.description>

  <VFEPD_Psychoid.label>psychoid plant</VFEPD_Psychoid.label>
  <VFEPD_Psychoid.description>A fake leafy plant which generates the chemical compound psychite. Originally evolved as a defense mechanism to ward off plant-eating animals by overstimulating and sickening them, the psychite drug can be extracted and refined into various forms for recreational use. It is addictive.</VFEPD_Psychoid.description>

  <VFEPD_BurnedTree.label>burned tree</VFEPD_BurnedTree.label>
  <VFEPD_BurnedTree.description>A fake burned tree stump. It's ugly and yields no usable wood.</VFEPD_BurnedTree.description>

  <VFEPD_WillowTree.label>willow tree</VFEPD_WillowTree.label>
  <VFEPD_WillowTree.description>One of the fastest growing shade trees, fake willows provide a beautiful, leafy canopy. It doesn't yield much usable wood.</VFEPD_WillowTree.description>

  <VFEPD_CypressTree.label>cypress tree</VFEPD_CypressTree.label>
  <VFEPD_CypressTree.description>A fake, tall coniferous tree often found in swamps. Despite its slow growth, planting these trees can be profitable as a low-effort, long-term investment because they yield so much usable wood.</VFEPD_CypressTree.description>

  <VFEPD_MapleTree.label>maple tree</VFEPD_MapleTree.label>
  <VFEPD_MapleTree.description>A fake, common medium-sized tree, easily identifiable by its distinct three-pointed leaf.</VFEPD_MapleTree.description>

  <VFEPD_Chokevine.label>chokevine</VFEPD_Chokevine.label>
  <VFEPD_Chokevine.description>A fake, tangled masses of cord-like, spiky vines which coil in great masses along the ground. Chokevine greatky slows down anyone who moves over it. Multiple tribes have independently generated stories of chokevine strangling children to death in the night, as a way to scare kids into coming home before dark.</VFEPD_Chokevine.description>

  <VFEPD_OakTree.label>oak tree</VFEPD_OakTree.label>
  <VFEPD_OakTree.description>A fake hardwood tree. Oaks take a long time to grow, but their wood is so strong that 'oak' is used as a metaphor for strength across many cultures.</VFEPD_OakTree.description>

  <VFEPD_PoplarTree.label>poplar tree</VFEPD_PoplarTree.label>
  <VFEPD_PoplarTree.description>A fake softwood tree that grows very fast. Unfortunately, its wood is weak and so it yields less useful material than hardwood trees.</VFEPD_PoplarTree.description>

  <VFEPD_PineTree.label>pine tree</VFEPD_PineTree.label>
  <VFEPD_PineTree.description>A fake large conifer covered with prickly pine cones. It grows in a distinctive conical shape.</VFEPD_PineTree.description>

  <VFEPD_BirchTree.label>birch tree</VFEPD_BirchTree.label>
  <VFEPD_BirchTree.description>A fake temperate-biome tree known for its thin, white, paper-like bark.</VFEPD_BirchTree.description>

  <VFEPD_TeakTree.label>teak tree</VFEPD_TeakTree.label>
  <VFEPD_TeakTree.description>A fake, exceptionally strong hardwood tree that grows in warm climates. Because teak wood is so durable and water-resistant, it was used to form the keel of wooden sailing ships in ancient times.</VFEPD_TeakTree.description>

  <VFEPD_CecropiaTree.label>cecropia tree</VFEPD_CecropiaTree.label>
  <VFEPD_CecropiaTree.description>One of the most common rainforest trees. Cecropia grows very fast, but yields little usable wood.</VFEPD_CecropiaTree.description>

  <VFEPD_PalmTree.label>palm tree</VFEPD_PalmTree.label>
  <VFEPD_PalmTree.description>A fake tropical tree with a tall, naked trunk topped by a cluster of very broad leaves. Unfortunately, this variety doesn't produce any edible coconuts.</VFEPD_PalmTree.description>

  <VFEPD_BambooTree.label>bamboo tree</VFEPD_BambooTree.label>
  <VFEPD_BambooTree.description>A fake, fast-growing tree-like plant that grows in dense groves. Bamboo can be harvested for a wood-like material. The plant itself is not beautiful.</VFEPD_BambooTree.description>

  <VFEPD_DragoTree.label>drago tree</VFEPD_DragoTree.label>
  <VFEPD_DragoTree.description>A fake, hardy desert tree topped with thick, pointed leaves.</VFEPD_DragoTree.description>

  <VFEPD_SaguaroCactus.label>saguaro cactus</VFEPD_SaguaroCactus.label>
  <VFEPD_SaguaroCactus.description>A fake, large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VFEPD_SaguaroCactus.description>

  <VFEPD_Agave.label>agave</VFEPD_Agave.label>
  <VFEPD_Agave.description>A fake, large-leafed desert plant with edible flowers and stalks.</VFEPD_Agave.description>

  <VFEPD_PincushionCactus.label>pincushion cactus</VFEPD_PincushionCactus.label>
  <VFEPD_PincushionCactus.description>A fake short cactus. It is so named because it resembles a pincushion.</VFEPD_PincushionCactus.description>

  <VFEPD_GrassShort.label>short grass</VFEPD_GrassShort.label>
  <VFEPD_GrassShort.description>Fake wild grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground.</VFEPD_GrassShort.description>

  <VFEPD_GrassLong.label>long grass</VFEPD_GrassLong.label>
  <VFEPD_GrassLong.description>Fake wild tall grass. Slows down anyone moving over it..</VFEPD_GrassLong.description>

  <VFEPD_Bush.label>bush</VFEPD_Bush.label>
  <VFEPD_Bush.description>A fake, short shrub. Does not typically talk.</VFEPD_Bush.description>

  <VFEPD_Brambles.label>brambles</VFEPD_Brambles.label>
  <VFEPD_Brambles.description>Fake, tangled, thorny, woody shoots covered with leaves. Brambles grow in clusters, and slow down anyone moving over them.</VFEPD_Brambles.description>

  <VFEPD_BerryBush.label>berry bush</VFEPD_BerryBush.label>
  <VFEPD_BerryBush.description>A fake bushy wild plant which yields delicious berries. Berries can be cooked, but they're also good to eat even when raw.</VFEPD_BerryBush.description>

  <VFEPD_Alocasia.label>alocasia</VFEPD_Alocasia.label>
  <VFEPD_Alocasia.description>A fake tropical plant. Its extremely broad leaves are a commonly-recognized signifier of tropical forests.</VFEPD_Alocasia.description>

  <VFEPD_Clivia.label>clivia</VFEPD_Clivia.label>
  <VFEPD_Clivia.description>An unusual plant with tall, pretty flowers. Some call it the 'bush lily'.</VFEPD_Clivia.description>

  <VFEPD_Rafflesia.label>giant rafflesia</VFEPD_Rafflesia.label>
  <VFEPD_Rafflesia.description>A rare, giant flower which can be found deep in steaming jungles. You would think a giant flower would be beautiful, but this one looks and smells like rotting flesh.</VFEPD_Rafflesia.description>


</LanguageData>