<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: Pirate chef -->
  <VBE_PirateChef.title>пиратский повар</VBE_PirateChef.title>
  <!-- EN: Chef -->
  <VBE_PirateChef.titleShort>повар</VBE_PirateChef.titleShort>
  <!-- EN: [PAWN_nameDef] was the Chef on a pirate ship. Between meals, they told tall tales that kept the crew's morale high. The crew's loyalty to their chef was great, possibly even greater than to their captain... -->
  <VBE_PirateChef.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} {PAWN_gender ? был : была} шеф-поваром на пиратском корабле. Во время приёмов пищи команда любила рассказывать своему повару разные истории. Весёлые беседы позволяли отвлечься от трудностей жизни и наладить хорошие отношения с поваром. Со временем преданность команды повару стала настолько высока, что начала угрожать капитану...</VBE_PirateChef.baseDescription>

  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.title>Gene-modded beauty</VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.title>
  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.titleShort>Beauty</VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.titleShort>
  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] Is the result of some of their home glitterworld's most advanced cosmetic surgery. During [PAWN_objective]  life they spent an untold fortune on their looks, they didn't have much time for to practice any more practical of skills. </VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.baseDescription>

  <VBE_HumanFarm.title>Human farm</VBE_HumanFarm.title>
  <VBE_HumanFarm.titleShort>Meat</VBE_HumanFarm.titleShort>
  <VBE_HumanFarm.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made only for one purpose, consumption. Grown out of a spindly set of hormone and development injectors connected to a solution-filled tube, many years of [PAWN_possessive] life was spent peering out into the lab, where butchers and scientists went on with their daily lives. During a freak accident which collapsed the farm, [PAWN_nameDef] escaped.
This gave a basic understanding of human anatomy to [PAWN_name Def], but scarred [PAWN_objective] for life. </VBE_HumanFarm.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Housecarl.title>Housecarl</VBE_Housecarl.title>
  <VBE_Housecarl.titleShort>Housecarl</VBE_Housecarl.titleShort>
  <VBE_Housecarl.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a housecarl to a powerful chieftain. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained in a variety of weapons, and was always armed both on and off the field of battle. After a conflict with a more powerful clan left [PAWN_possessive] chieftain and many clan members dead, [PAWN_pronoun] left to find a new house to lend [PAWN_possessive] blade, or simply do something new entirely. </VBE_Housecarl.baseDescription>

  <VBE_FanaticInventor.title>Fanatic inventor</VBE_FanaticInventor.title>
  <VBE_FanaticInventor.titleShort>Inventor</VBE_FanaticInventor.titleShort>
  <VBE_FanaticInventor.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef]'s love for machinery and engineering is downright fanatic. In [PAWN_possessive] Urbworld home, [PAWN_pronoun] made illegal drones, guns and machines, often being chased by the police. [PAWN_nameDef] doesn't see nature as anything other than a source of materials to be refined into something useful.</VBE_FanaticInventor.baseDescription>

  <VBE_CaveinSurvivor.title>Cave-in survivor</VBE_CaveinSurvivor.title>
  <VBE_CaveinSurvivor.titleShort>Survivor</VBE_CaveinSurvivor.titleShort>
  <VBE_CaveinSurvivor.baseDescription>Forced into thralldom after [PAWN_possessive] clan was destroyed, [PAWN_nameDef] was quickly thrown into the mines, digging for precious metals. Due to a lack of safety and care for [PAWN_objective] life from [PAWN_objective] captors, the mine collapsed, leaving [PAWN_nameDef] as the only survivor. To ensure [PAWN_pronoun] never needs to return, [PAWN_pronoun] became an adept artisan, and would at times become violent when pressed towards the mines.</VBE_CaveinSurvivor.baseDescription>

  <VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.title>Industrial gunsmith </VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.title>
  <VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.titleShort>Gunsmith</VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.titleShort>
  <VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] days meticulously working at [PAWN_possessive] machining table to create firearms. [PAWN_pronoun] spent several hours at the gun range to test out [PAWN_possessive] new designs. However, spending so much time working with firearms has left [PAWN_objective] rather deficient in close range combat.   </VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.baseDescription>

  <VBE_SlaveTrader.title>Slave trader</VBE_SlaveTrader.title>
  <VBE_SlaveTrader.titleShort>Slaver</VBE_SlaveTrader.titleShort>
  <VBE_SlaveTrader.baseDescription>Realizing the profit bodies bring when warm instead of cold, [PAWN_nameDef] would insist [PAWN_possessive] clan take as many prisoners as possible during a raid, employing nets, bolas, and other items that could be thrown towards those fleeing. When the fighting was over, [PAWN_pronoun] would travel, peddling [PAWN_possessive] wares in various kingdoms. Always having thralls around has made [PAWN_nameDef] adverse to so-called "slave work," and generally less compassionate. </VBE_SlaveTrader.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ModelCitizen.title>Model citizen</VBE_ModelCitizen.title>
  <VBE_ModelCitizen.titleShort>Citizen</VBE_ModelCitizen.titleShort>
  <VBE_ModelCitizen.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] lived a criminal life, a very violent one, but was caught. Instead of being executed or sent to prison, [PAWN_pronoun] was sent to try an experimental psychological treatment that would make [PAWN_possessive] a good member of society again. While the nature and morality of the program was questionable, the results were definitive, [PAWN_pronoun] is now a model citizen. </VBE_ModelCitizen.baseDescription>

  <VBE_MidworldNomad.title>Midworld nomad</VBE_MidworldNomad.title>
  <VBE_MidworldNomad.titleShort>Nomad child</VBE_MidworldNomad.titleShort>
  <VBE_MidworldNomad.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] spent their younger years on a midworld studying variety of both modern and historical subjects including agriculture, engineering and politics. After their transport pod crashed on a Medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef] was heralded as summoned champion sent by the Gods, in then next few years [PAWN_nameDef] started to introduce several cultural, technological, and societal reforms that would drastically improve the quality of life on this world.</VBE_MidworldNomad.baseDescription>

  <VBE_DogWalker.title>Dog walker</VBE_DogWalker.title>
  <VBE_DogWalker.titleShort>Walker</VBE_DogWalker.titleShort>
  <VBE_DogWalker.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] enjoys being around animals so much, they volunteered at their local shelter to help walk the dogs and give them some exercise. That lasted until [PAWN_pronoun] realized how lucrative of a business it could be and [PAWN_nameDef] scaled up operations to become a full time dog walker with dozens of clients. </VBE_DogWalker.baseDescription>

  <VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.title>Starfighter maintainer</VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.title>
  <VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.titleShort>Mechanic</VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.titleShort>
  <VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] served on carrier ships in campaigns across [PAWN_possessive] home system, working to keep the starfighters and transports in fighting shape. While [PAWN_pronoun] knows just about everything there is to know about spacecraft maintenance, [PAWN_possessive] reliance on following repair manuals to the letter has had a negative impact on [PAWN_possessive] lateral thinking.</VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Watchman.title>Watchman</VBE_Watchman.title>
  <VBE_Watchman.titleShort>Watchman</VBE_Watchman.titleShort>
  <VBE_Watchman.baseDescription>Not the strongest fighter, [PAWN_nameDef] was placed on watchtower duty. Watching the comings and goings of those passing through the town's gate made for a very boring life, causing [PAWN_objective] to start cooking in [PAWN_possessive] wooden tower. One day [PAWN_pronoun] accidentally knocked over the cauldron, sending coals everywhere. The tower quickly caught ablaze and burned to ash. [PAWN_pronoun] survived, but was never the same around fire. </VBE_Watchman.baseDescription>

  <VBE_FashionDesigner.title>Fashion designer</VBE_FashionDesigner.title>
  <VBE_FashionDesigner.titleShort>Seamstress</VBE_FashionDesigner.titleShort>
  <VBE_FashionDesigner.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] always said the world was never ready for [PAWN_possessive] creations, but [PAWN_pronoun] was going to be fabulous anyway. With [PAWN_possessive] trusty sewing machine, [PAWN_nameDef] went from runway to runway trying to make a name for [PAWN_objective]self.</VBE_FashionDesigner.baseDescription>

  <VBE_AimlessDilettante.title>Aimless dilettante</VBE_AimlessDilettante.title>
  <VBE_AimlessDilettante.titleShort>Dilettante</VBE_AimlessDilettante.titleShort>
  <VBE_AimlessDilettante.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into privilege but never quite knew what to do with [PAWN_possessive] life. Despite skilled tutors for everything from fencing to horticulture, [PAWN_pronoun] never really excelled at anything.</VBE_AimlessDilettante.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>