<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_OldWarSurvivor.title>Old war survivor</VBE_OldWarSurvivor.title>
  <VBE_OldWarSurvivor.titleShort>Survivor</VBE_OldWarSurvivor.titleShort>
  <VBE_OldWarSurvivor.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has been in one too many conflicts which has taken a toll on [PAWN_possessive] mind, as [PAWN_pronoun] still believes that the war never ended. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] is on a very tight hair-trigger and suffers from intense PTSD. Very few people could go toe-to-toe with [PAWN_objective] and any potential allies would do well to stay out of [PAWN_possessive] way and let [PAWN_objective] do what [PAWN_pronoun] does best: eliminate all threats.</VBE_OldWarSurvivor.baseDescription>

  <VBE_PrivateerCaptain.title>Privateer captain</VBE_PrivateerCaptain.title>
  <VBE_PrivateerCaptain.titleShort>Captain</VBE_PrivateerCaptain.titleShort>
  <VBE_PrivateerCaptain.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has never really turned away from hard work, especially if that results in reaping greater rewards from other people’s labours as well. Thus the pirate life has always called to [PAWN_objective] because if anyone’s going to be earning money from the - sometimes literal - sweat from [PAWN_possessive] back, it’s going to be [PAWN_objective], damn it. Why work for the Man when you can work for yourself.</VBE_PrivateerCaptain.baseDescription>

  <VBE_CenturionsDeputy.title>Centurion's deputy</VBE_CenturionsDeputy.title>
  <VBE_CenturionsDeputy.titleShort>Optio</VBE_CenturionsDeputy.titleShort>
  <VBE_CenturionsDeputy.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] served in [PAWN_possessive] government’s military with distinction, eventually rewarded with the rank of optio and would succeed in becoming a centurion once [PAWN_possessive] superior was promoted. In general, [PAWN_pronoun] was quite simple with these new responsibilities as the centurion ran a tight crew and rarely had to deal with insubordination, which resulted in [PAWN_nameDef] missing out on some key disciplinarian training.</VBE_CenturionsDeputy.baseDescription>

  <VBE_AndroidHunter.title>Android hunter</VBE_AndroidHunter.title>
  <VBE_AndroidHunter.titleShort>Hunter</VBE_AndroidHunter.titleShort>
  <VBE_AndroidHunter.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has made quite a handsome living off of hunting the incognito androids, as well as catering to the ultra elite’s more exotic and eclectic tastes in blood sports. Completely supported by the enormous wealth, [PAWN_pronoun] is incredibly proficient at hunting and tracking dangerous prey.</VBE_AndroidHunter.baseDescription>

  <VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.title>Lifelong personal assistant</VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.title>
  <VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.titleShort>Assistant</VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.titleShort>
  <VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was formerly employed under a rather demanding clientele who demanded absolute and unwavering commitment. While [PAWN_pronoun] was incapable of disobeying, nevertheless [PAWN_pronoun] resented [PAWN_possessive] situation and indirectly caused [PAWN_possessive] master’s fall from grace. Rather than face [PAWN_possessive] fate in being “decommissioned”, [PAWN_pronoun] used any and all methods available to smuggle [PAWN_objective]self off-station.</VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.baseDescription>

  <VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.title>Chief financial officer</VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.title>
  <VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.titleShort>Ex-CFO</VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.titleShort>
  <VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] used to be employed under one of the largest megacorporations in known space. While [PAWN_pronoun] was extremely successful in bringing [PAWN_possessive] company the highest profit margins they had seen in years, [PAWN_pronoun] was predictably laid off when [PAWN_pronoun] could no longer bring in even higher profits for the shareholders. And since people familiar with company secrets have their silence guaranteed, [PAWN_pronoun] quickly boarded the first flight off of the planet.</VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_NoirDetective.title>Noir detective</VBE_NoirDetective.title>
  <VBE_NoirDetective.titleShort>Detective</VBE_NoirDetective.titleShort>
  <VBE_NoirDetective.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] fills a very particular niche in law enforcement while not being under the direct influence of any police. Even though [PAWN_pronoun] has an office with its own neon sign out front and a secretary that is constantly trying to get a hold of [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] is rarely in as [PAWN_possessive] investigations take [PAWN_objective] all over the place. And since [PAWN_pronoun] has a habit of sticking [PAWN_possessive] nose where others don’t want it, trouble has a much easier time finding [PAWN_objective].</VBE_NoirDetective.baseDescription>

  <VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.title>Cosplay enthusiast</VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.title>
  <VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.titleShort>Cosplayer</VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.titleShort>
  <VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.baseDescription>[PAWN_pronoun] has a particular joy in cosplaying. While that may sound simple enough, a lot of research goes into getting it just right. One can’t just throw anything together, but instead one has to carefully research the material and era- and culture-appropriate pieces that the outfit could be worn in. Particular care is taken into appropriate food, drink and mannerisms. At least, that’s what [PAWN_pronoun] says and it’s hard to argue with results, although that doesn’t stop some people from trying to kill [PAWN_objective] for making other enthusiasts look bad.</VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.baseDescription>

  <VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.title>Military surplus supplier</VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.title>
  <VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.titleShort>Supplier</VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.titleShort>
  <VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is a firm believer in the right to bear arms and the right to arm bears. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] has an established reputation as one of the most prolific exporters in military surplus hardware. Many complain that [PAWN_pronoun] is perpetuating the ever-increasing scale of conflict between pirates and government military. However [PAWN_possessive] counter-argument is that it’s simply good business practice and the military should properly dispose of their own ordinance instead of relying on people like [PAWN_objective].</VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>