<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_Sommelier.title>Sommelier </VBE_Sommelier.title>
  <VBE_Sommelier.titleShort>Sommelier </VBE_Sommelier.titleShort>
  <VBE_Sommelier.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was an experienced winemaker, growing [PAWN_possessive] own grapes and putting utmost care into [PAWN_possessive] work. [PAWN_pronoun] also is quite fond of cooking meals to pair with [PAWN_possessive] wines.</VBE_Sommelier.baseDescription>

  <VBE_DesertSurvivor.title>Desert survivor</VBE_DesertSurvivor.title>
  <VBE_DesertSurvivor.titleShort>Survivor</VBE_DesertSurvivor.titleShort>
  <VBE_DesertSurvivor.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef]'s sworn enemies left [PAWN_objective] to die on a hostile desert planet. Despite all the odds, [PAWN_pronoun] survived in such an environment and adapted to it. Due to spending a lot of time living in the wastelands, [PAWN_nameDef] has no knowledge about plants.</VBE_DesertSurvivor.baseDescription>

  <VBE_LiteraryCritic.title>Literary critic</VBE_LiteraryCritic.title>
  <VBE_LiteraryCritic.titleShort>Critic</VBE_LiteraryCritic.titleShort>
  <VBE_LiteraryCritic.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] partook in formal education in Literature, obtaining the highest score in [PAWN_objective] class and even in the history of that department’s founding. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] takes almost sadistic pleasure in critiquing people’s work, especially if they are otherwise considered their magnum opus. Many bestselling authors have been reduced to tears by [PAWN_objective] harsh judgement, which often results in their life’s work becoming publicly despised.</VBE_LiteraryCritic.baseDescription>

  <VBE_RodentRancher.title>Rodent rancher</VBE_RodentRancher.title>
  <VBE_RodentRancher.titleShort>Rancher</VBE_RodentRancher.titleShort>
  <VBE_RodentRancher.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] spent a lot of [PAWN_objective] time working on a rodent farm in an overpopulated city on one of the urbworlds. Due to limited spacing and mostly processed foods, [PAWN_pronoun] found great success in offering actual meat for those who wanted a break from mediocrity. Granted [PAWN_pronoun] ended up on the run because [PAWN_possessive] Ratburgers attracted the taxman, but [PAWN_pronoun] found it fun while it lasted.</VBE_RodentRancher.baseDescription>

  <VBE_PathologicalLiar.title>Pathological liar</VBE_PathologicalLiar.title>
  <VBE_PathologicalLiar.titleShort>Liar</VBE_PathologicalLiar.titleShort>
  <VBE_PathologicalLiar.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] loves to make stuff up and just can’t help [PAWN_objective]self. Particularly, [PAWN_pronoun] enjoys going to any place that serves alcohol and tells the biggest, boldest stories full of twists, turns and drama while being bought round after round. However, once [PAWN_pronoun] gets bored or has decided that [PAWN_pronoun] has drunk enough, almost every story ends on a completely random note with everyone dying in horrific fashion.</VBE_PathologicalLiar.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Blackguard.title>Blackguard</VBE_Blackguard.title>
  <VBE_Blackguard.titleShort>Blackguard</VBE_Blackguard.titleShort>
  <VBE_Blackguard.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] never really managed well wherever [PAWN_pronoun] went as a general air of misfortune seemingly hovers over [PAWN_possessive] head. As most people are extremely superstitious, every town [PAWN_pronoun] has visited has chased [PAWN_objective] away as disaster always seems to follow while [PAWN_pronoun] survives. So [PAWN_pronoun] got really good at fending for [PAWN_objective]self.</VBE_Blackguard.baseDescription>

  <VBE_BountyHunter.title>Bounty hunter</VBE_BountyHunter.title>
  <VBE_BountyHunter.titleShort>Hunter</VBE_BountyHunter.titleShort>
  <VBE_BountyHunter.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] takes a lot of pride in [PAWN_possessive] to find, capture and deliver individuals who have pissed off the wrong people, primarily if it involves a large cash influx in [PAWN_possessive] direction. It might not be the most glamorous job but it pays for a decent lifestyle and that’s all [PAWN_pronoun] has ever really wanted in life. Plus [PAWN_pronoun] gets to shoot people in the face, which can be surprisingly therapeutic.</VBE_BountyHunter.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Thane.title>Thane</VBE_Thane.title>
  <VBE_Thane.titleShort>Thane</VBE_Thane.titleShort>
  <VBE_Thane.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was elevated to a position of thane in [PAWN_possessive] jarl’s holding, giving [PAWN_possessive] a large degree of freedom to do as [PAWN_pronoun] pleased as long as it advanced their interests. So far [PAWN_pronoun] has enjoyed an easier life with a few servants while taking up an interest in raising beasts of war and training elite soldiers.</VBE_Thane.baseDescription>

  <VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.title>Trainee combat medic</VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.title>
  <VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.titleShort>Paramedic</VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.titleShort>
  <VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has received extensive military training to act as the lynchpin for [PAWN_possessive] squad. This includes but is not limited to recovering and treating wounded soldiers or people of interest, as well as acting as second-in-command. While this doesn’t detract from the results, [PAWN_pronoun] has an extremely dry, no-nonsense personality and can be difficult to get along with.</VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>