<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_Barber.title>Barber</VBE_Barber.title>
  <VBE_Barber.titleShort>Barber</VBE_Barber.titleShort>
  <VBE_Barber.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a barber, cutting and styling hair. Knows their way around a pair of scissors and can keep conversations going with [PAWN_possessive] clients.</VBE_Barber.baseDescription>

  <VBE_AddictedGamer.title>Addicted gamer</VBE_AddictedGamer.title>
  <VBE_AddictedGamer.titleShort>Gamer</VBE_AddictedGamer.titleShort>
  <VBE_AddictedGamer.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has an addiction to video games and can often be found gaming late into the morning. [PAWN_possessive] fits all the negative stereotypes from the messy room to the social awkwardness, but at least [PAWN_objective]'s learned a few things about crafting and mining.</VBE_AddictedGamer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_VatgrownColonist.title>Vatgrown colonist</VBE_VatgrownColonist.title>
  <VBE_VatgrownColonist.titleShort>Colonist</VBE_VatgrownColonist.titleShort>
  <VBE_VatgrownColonist.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was grown in a lab as an expendable body on [PAWN_objective] Glitterworld. [PAWN_pronoun] was raised along with the other grown standard template children and only knew life under their scientist guides. </VBE_VatgrownColonist.baseDescription>

  <VBE_StructuralEngineer.title>Structural engineer</VBE_StructuralEngineer.title>
  <VBE_StructuralEngineer.titleShort>Engineer</VBE_StructuralEngineer.titleShort>
  <VBE_StructuralEngineer.baseDescription>After studying engineering for a few years, [PAWN_nameDef] now designs buildings, bridges, and other structures. [PAWN_objective] has a great understanding on how to construct every part of a project. Much of their time goes to coordinating with the architect, contractor, and other engineers.</VBE_StructuralEngineer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_WretchedChild.title>Wretched child</VBE_WretchedChild.title>
  <VBE_WretchedChild.titleShort>Wretch</VBE_WretchedChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_WretchedChild.baseDescription>As a child, [PAWN_nameDef] was cast out by [PAWN_objective] peers. [PAWN_pronoun] grew uncaring of others and focused on surviving with what [PAWN_pronoun] had near [PAWN_possessive] home.</VBE_WretchedChild.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.title>Forced primitivist</VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.title>
  <VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.titleShort>Primitivist </VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.titleShort>
  <VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] wasn't always part of the tribes. After getting exiled from [PAWN_possessive] local outlander union due to ruining an entire crop harvest, [PAWN_nameDef] had to live out in the open for years, with only crude tools to aid [PAWN_objective]. This made [PAWN_objective] a jack-of-all-trades, but completely broke [PAWN_possessive] trust of people.  </VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.baseDescription>

  <VBE_GiftedBurnout.title>Gifted burnout</VBE_GiftedBurnout.title>
  <VBE_GiftedBurnout.titleShort>Gifted</VBE_GiftedBurnout.titleShort>
  <VBE_GiftedBurnout.baseDescription>From a young age, [PAWN_nameDef] was heralded as a genius. The constant testing, training, and praise from surrounding adults was good, but the constant pressure, expectation, and eventual failure exacerbated a long list of mental disorders lying dormant within [PAWN_nameDef]'s mind. [PAWN_pronoun] still retains [PAWN_objective] training, but making use of it will be difficult for the rest of [PAWN_objective] life.</VBE_GiftedBurnout.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ForgottenChild.title>Forgotten child</VBE_ForgottenChild.title>
  <VBE_ForgottenChild.titleShort>Disappeared</VBE_ForgottenChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_ForgottenChild.baseDescription>When [PAWN_nameDef] was young [PAWN_pronoun] came across a secret door in [PAWN_possessive] grandfather's antic shop. Curious of what may lie beyond it, [PAWN_pronoun] wandered in and tells of a land of endless adventure. There's no way of knowing if that were true, but seeing as [PAWN_nameDef] was found as child, forgotten in cryptosleep nearly a hundred years later, nothing seems impossible.</VBE_ForgottenChild.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Demoscener.title>Demoscener</VBE_Demoscener.title>
  <VBE_Demoscener.titleShort>Demoscener</VBE_Demoscener.titleShort>
  <VBE_Demoscener.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has always been interested in computers and programming. Specifically the computers which are so old that the line between programming and engineering is blurred. [PAWN_nameDef] has fallen in with a culture that uses these ancient machines to create art, using the full extent of the primitive programming available.</VBE_Demoscener.baseDescription>

  <VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.title>Industrial tinkerer</VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.title>
  <VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.titleShort>Tinkerer</VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.titleShort>
  <VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.baseDescription>Once finding [PAWN_possessive] passion in the way things work, [PAWN_nameDef] became enthralled with tinkering, building and coding. Taking inspiration from nature and the machines [PAWN_pronoun] disassembled, [PAWN_nameDef] built many useful mechanical and electrical contraptions to improve [PAWN_possessive] everyday life. While exploring and studying nature, [PAWN_pronoun] also learned about basic survival needs, and some basic healing. Due to always being in [PAWN_possessive] mind, [PAWN_nameDef] is not very sociable, and [PAWN_possessive] is always high strung.</VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_InformationSponge.title>Information sponge</VBE_InformationSponge.title>
  <VBE_InformationSponge.titleShort>Sponge</VBE_InformationSponge.titleShort>
  <VBE_InformationSponge.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up with a thirst for knowledge, be it for science, history, or philosophy. Running off into the wilderness, [PAWN_pronoun] would spend as much time learning from nature and the ruins that [PAWN_pronoun] would find. When younger, many would listen to [PAWN_objective] just to see what [PAWN_pronoun] would say, but over time others stopped listening as [PAWN_possessive] knowledge grew in depth, leaving them behind. Over time, [PAWN_pronoun] became more reclusive, and mainly found solace in [PAWN_possessive] work. </VBE_InformationSponge.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.title>Reincarnated soul</VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.title>
  <VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.titleShort>Reincarnated</VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.titleShort>
  <VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] believes [PAWN_pronoun] was once a pious steward of some long, lost religion. Reborn again to live life as they choose, [PAWN_nameDef] seems to have an unnatural proficiency with cooking and art of craft despite [PAWN_objective] young age.</VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.baseDescription>

  <VBE_LightingAssistant.title>Lighting assistant</VBE_LightingAssistant.title>
  <VBE_LightingAssistant.titleShort>Lighter</VBE_LightingAssistant.titleShort>
  <VBE_LightingAssistant.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] helped make the background lighting in films and shows. Working behind the scenes completely undetected, [PAWN_pronoun] was never acknowledged by higher-ups, and just opted to work harder until somebody noticed [PAWN_possessive] talent. All the tinkering with electrical equipment gave [PAWN_nameDef] a distinct knowledge of manufacturing.</VBE_LightingAssistant.baseDescription>

  <VBE_SiloManager.title>Silo manager</VBE_SiloManager.title>
  <VBE_SiloManager.titleShort>Manager</VBE_SiloManager.titleShort>
  <VBE_SiloManager.baseDescription>Urbworlds are filled with massive resource silos, half a kilometer high and several kilometers across, with thousands of barely-paid workers carrying materials like little ants across the vast complex. [PAWN_nameDef] worked as a manager to one of the silos, and didn't even have to stand up from [PAWN_possessive] desk. </VBE_SiloManager.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Pushover.title>Pushover</VBE_Pushover.title>
  <VBE_Pushover.titleShort>Pushover</VBE_Pushover.titleShort>
  <VBE_Pushover.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a pushover and a severe social outcast. Being constantly bullied, [PAWN_pronoun] gained a distaste towards other people. All the nights being forced to do other people's homework made for great test results, though. </VBE_Pushover.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>