<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_IncompetentPilot.title>Incompetent pilot</VBE_IncompetentPilot.title>
  <VBE_IncompetentPilot.titleShort>Incompetent</VBE_IncompetentPilot.titleShort>
  <VBE_IncompetentPilot.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a helmsman of a large cargo vessel. An unfortunate series of events, some of which were [PAWN_possessive] fault, resulted in the entirety of his crew being vaporized by his ship's fusion engine in a freak accident. Fearing reprisal, he hailed a passing pirate ship and managed to smooth talk [PAWN_possessive] way into safe passage to another world to restart his life, and hopefully forget about his past mistakes.</VBE_IncompetentPilot.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Marauder.title>Marauder</VBE_Marauder.title>
  <VBE_Marauder.titleShort>Marauder</VBE_Marauder.titleShort>
  <VBE_Marauder.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] life as a fighter in a nomadic fleet of space pirates until it dissolved from infighting. [PAWN_objective] saw many battles, but never even went close to any books.</VBE_Marauder.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ArchotechFanatic.title>Archotech fanatic</VBE_ArchotechFanatic.title>
  <VBE_ArchotechFanatic.titleShort>Archofanatic</VBE_ArchotechFanatic.titleShort>
  <VBE_ArchotechFanatic.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] claims that [PAWN_possessive] mind has been visited by an omnipotent entity that manifests itself through advanced archotech objects. While [PAWN_nameDef] shows great affinity towards technology and research, [PAWN_pronoun] harbors equally strong disgust when it comes to plants and animals.</VBE_ArchotechFanatic.baseDescription>

  <VBE_PondDesigner.title>Pond designer</VBE_PondDesigner.title>
  <VBE_PondDesigner.titleShort>Gardener</VBE_PondDesigner.titleShort>
  <VBE_PondDesigner.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] created extravagant ponds for the wealthy. [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of aquatic flora and fauna and how they interact is unsurpassed. One day, a client introduced a new fish into one of [PAWN_possessive] pond, destroying the delicate ecosystem. That was the last drop for [PAWN_objective], who left everything behind and took the first ship to the Rim, where [PAWN_pronoun] hopes to realize [PAWN_possessive] dream: to design a whole new ecosystem on a planetary scale.</VBE_PondDesigner.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Cryonic.title>Cryonic</VBE_Cryonic.title>
  <VBE_Cryonic.titleShort>Cryonic</VBE_Cryonic.titleShort>
  <VBE_Cryonic.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is from a civilization that perished to an ice age that devastated [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [PAWN_possessive] body was preserved in the ice for centuries until [PAWN_pronoun] was recovered by a glitterworld archaeological expedition, and was resuscitated with advanced mechanite serums on their planet. Unwilling to be kept as a research subject, [PAWN_nameDef] escaped with the help of a group of humanitarian activists. This experience made [PAWN_objective] distrustful of strangers, but [PAWN_pronoun] also picked up some knowledge from [PAWN_possessive] time in the laboratory.</VBE_Cryonic.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Masterofceremonies.title>Master of ceremonies</VBE_Masterofceremonies.title>
  <VBE_Masterofceremonies.titleShort>Arbiter</VBE_Masterofceremonies.titleShort>
  <VBE_Masterofceremonies.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a master of ceremonies. [PAWN_pronoun] trained for decades just to meet the minimal requirements for the job: [PAWN_pronoun] had to memorize the thousands of complicated rituals ruling diplomatic meetings on his world, including the correct way to execute one who makes a mistake. In [PAWN_possessive] culture, war has all but disappeared: nobody has ever managed to get to the end of the ritual required to declare war without making a mistake. [PAWN_pronoun] now hopes to bring the same peace to the Rim, one ritual at a time.</VBE_Masterofceremonies.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.title>Chemfuel farmer</VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.title>
  <VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.titleShort>Farmer</VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.titleShort>
  <VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is an entrepreneur. [PAWN_pronoun] recognized immediately how much money was to be made with chemfuel, a substance so widely used that demand never seems to go down, no matter how much of the stuff you sell. [PAWN_pronoun] first convinced [PAWN_possessive] family to buy a boomalope ranch, then his neighbors to plant chemroot. Soon, the whole town was refining everything they could get their hands on. Since the storm of last summer, [PAWN_pronoun] has been looking for a new town to live in. Anywhere, really: he has no family to tie him down.</VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_CoginTheMachine.title>Cog in the machine</VBE_CoginTheMachine.title>
  <VBE_CoginTheMachine.titleShort>Cog</VBE_CoginTheMachine.titleShort>
  <VBE_CoginTheMachine.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a very organized and efficient world. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained from birth to do one very specialized job: to paint one specific screw in a specific shade of gray. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] decided to paint the screws green. The other workers couldn't cope with this unforeseen change and stopped working. The chaos spread, and [PAWN_nameDef] soon had to flee a world plunged in anarchy.</VBE_CoginTheMachine.baseDescription>

  <VBE_TrainDriver.title>Train driver</VBE_TrainDriver.title>
  <VBE_TrainDriver.titleShort>Engineer</VBE_TrainDriver.titleShort>
  <VBE_TrainDriver.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] loves trains. [PAWN_pronoun] used to drive a steam-powered locomotive on a small line in an idyllic landscape. [PAWN_pronoun] would greet the sleepy villages along the line each morning with the cheery sound of the horn. [PAWN_possessive] only worry was to shovel enough coal to keep the locomotive running and to repair the train from time to time. One day, he had to stop in a village. An enraged and sleep-deprived mob took the opportunity to destroy the train and [PAWN_nameDef] decided to leave before they remembered who was responsible for sounding the horn.</VBE_TrainDriver.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ClonedHeir.title>Cloned heir</VBE_ClonedHeir.title>
  <VBE_ClonedHeir.titleShort>Clone</VBE_ClonedHeir.titleShort>
  <VBE_ClonedHeir.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was created to replace the missing heir of a noble house, but did not turn out quite right. Despite the best efforts of [PAWN_possessive] tutors, [PAWN_pronoun] was far more interested in bloodshed than the intricacies of the court.

When the heir turned out to be alive after all, [PAWN_nameDef] was discarded to make room for [PAWN_possessive] genetic source.</VBE_ClonedHeir.baseDescription>

  <VBE_MedicineProdigy.title>Medicine prodigy</VBE_MedicineProdigy.title>
  <VBE_MedicineProdigy.titleShort>Prodigy</VBE_MedicineProdigy.titleShort>
  <VBE_MedicineProdigy.baseDescription>Born on an overpopulated urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef] displayed a remarkable aptitude for medicine from an early age. Plucked from the education system and inducted into a special program for the intellectually gifted, [PAWN_pronoun] received the best education money could buy, but little time to develop socially or engage in risky behaviour.

To [PAWN_possessive] benefactors, [PAWN_pronoun] was an expensive investment.</VBE_MedicineProdigy.baseDescription>

  <VBE_CorruptPolitician.title>Corrupt politician</VBE_CorruptPolitician.title>
  <VBE_CorruptPolitician.titleShort>Politician</VBE_CorruptPolitician.titleShort>
  <VBE_CorruptPolitician.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] had a gift for lying and getting away with it, a gift [PAWN_pronoun] used to get elected only to embezzle staggering sums. When [PAWN_possessive] lies finally caught up with [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] shot a peacekeeper and fled the planet.</VBE_CorruptPolitician.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.title>Imperial circus performer</VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.title>
  <VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.titleShort>Clown</VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.titleShort>
  <VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.baseDescription>Though [PAWN_pronoun] is known by [PAWN_possessive] friends as [PAWN_nameDef], throughout the systems [PAWN_pronoun] is known as [PAWN_nameDef] the Amazing. [PAWN_nameDef] has performed theatrics and acrobatic stunts and for the Imperial nobles. [PAWN_pronoun] will often brag about [PAWN_possessive] group of followers that attend [PAWN_possessive] every show. Though, no one really knows how many of [PAWN_possessive] stories are just made up. </VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_CorporateMascot.title>Corporate mascot</VBE_CorporateMascot.title>
  <VBE_CorporateMascot.titleShort>Mascot</VBE_CorporateMascot.titleShort>
  <VBE_CorporateMascot.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a costumed entertainer for a morally questionable entertainment corporation. [PAWN_pronoun] was forced to dance in a depressing white animal suit in exchange for meager pay.</VBE_CorporateMascot.baseDescription>

  <VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.title>Deep space scrapper</VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.title>
  <VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.titleShort>Scrapper</VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.titleShort>
  <VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.baseDescription>Due to the amount of recent interstellar battles, there are a lot of derelict ships floating in space. It's [PAWN_nameDef]'s job to find these ships and salvage them. [PAWN_nameDef] scraps ships, both in orbit and planetside wrecks, and sells the material and parts. Since the ownership of these ships can come into question, [PAWN_nameDef] sometimes finds [PAWN_objective]self on the wrong side of the law.   </VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>