<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_AquaponicWorker.title>Aquaponic worker</VBE_AquaponicWorker.title>
  <VBE_AquaponicWorker.titleShort>Fishfarmer</VBE_AquaponicWorker.titleShort>
  <VBE_AquaponicWorker.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] used to work in an aquaponic lab. He was tasked with the production of fish and vegetables for his colony. While PAWN_possessive] work was important it did leave little time for socializing.</VBE_AquaponicWorker.baseDescription>

  <VBE_StewCooker.title>Stew cooker</VBE_StewCooker.title>
  <VBE_StewCooker.titleShort>Cook</VBE_StewCooker.titleShort>
  <VBE_StewCooker.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] marched with long lines of medieval armies, and was in charge of the stew pots in the camps. [PAWN_possessive] know-how about some local plants and fungi allowed people to stretch ration for longer, and saved a life or two when the supplies ran dry.</VBE_StewCooker.baseDescription>

  <VBE_StarvingArtist.title>Starving artist</VBE_StarvingArtist.title>
  <VBE_StarvingArtist.titleShort>Artist</VBE_StarvingArtist.titleShort>
  <VBE_StarvingArtist.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was an relatively well-off art student in an urban world. A financial collapse forced [PAWN_objective] onto the streets, selling paintings for a living. [PAWN_pronoun] didn’t make much, and what surplus [PAWN_pronoun] had went into more materials and food for some friendly and loyal stray dogs.</VBE_StarvingArtist.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Foreman.title>Foreman</VBE_Foreman.title>
  <VBE_Foreman.titleShort>Foreman</VBE_Foreman.titleShort>
  <VBE_Foreman.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a foreman in a mine extracting industrial metals. [PAWN_pronoun] worked alongside the workers to ensure safety and motivate them. Workers under [PAWN_objective] were paid decently well, and liked [PAWN_possessive] leadership.</VBE_Foreman.baseDescription>

  <VBE_GalleryJanitor.title>Gallery janitor</VBE_GalleryJanitor.title>
  <VBE_GalleryJanitor.titleShort>Janitor</VBE_GalleryJanitor.titleShort>
  <VBE_GalleryJanitor.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a janitor in a modern art gallery, but never understood the appeal. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] decided to add a few strokes of paint to an asymmetrical artwork worth millions. [PAWN_nameDef] made headlines in the news, and [PAWN_pronoun] was fired and banned from the gallery.</VBE_GalleryJanitor.baseDescription>

  <VBE_HostessInTraining.title>Hostess in training</VBE_HostessInTraining.title>
  <VBE_HostessInTraining.titleShort>Hostess</VBE_HostessInTraining.titleShort>
  <VBE_HostessInTraining.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] spent plenty of time in their parent's restaurant growing up, eventually getting a job seating patrons. While they weren't a cook by trade, they still picked up a lot of the tastes and preferences of the clientele, along with plenty of gossip. This ended poorly one day after an altercation with an ex-lover, and they've been drifting since.</VBE_HostessInTraining.baseDescription>

  <VBE_TunerPunk.title>Tuner punk</VBE_TunerPunk.title>
  <VBE_TunerPunk.titleShort>Tuner</VBE_TunerPunk.titleShort>
  <VBE_TunerPunk.baseDescription>A bit of a loner, [PAWN_nameDef] found belonging and family in the mechanics who'd race modded-out cars. This led to many knife brawls, high-speed chases, and the occasional gunshot wound, but this didn't stop [PAWN_nameDef] from enjoying the competition.</VBE_TunerPunk.baseDescription>

  <VBE_OliveFarmer.title>Olive farmer</VBE_OliveFarmer.title>
  <VBE_OliveFarmer.titleShort>Farmer</VBE_OliveFarmer.titleShort>
  <VBE_OliveFarmer.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was the lucky owner of an olive tree plantation. [PAWN_pronoun] would spend hours tending the saplings, always telling [PAWN_possessive] family when they would laugh about it: never give up your last sapling, whatever happens, you can always start over. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] was found in a refugee group, staring blankly at his last possessions: a bloody picture and a small sapling. When it was time to go, [PAWN_pronoun] left the small olive tree behind.</VBE_OliveFarmer.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Florist.title>Florist</VBE_Florist.title>
  <VBE_Florist.titleShort>Florist</VBE_Florist.titleShort>
  <VBE_Florist.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is a gentle soul with a talent for creating new flower hybrids. [PAWN_pronoun] loved to create new flowers for all kinds of occasions, but was deeply distressed each time someone died. When the plague struck [PAWN_possessive] city, [PAWN_pronoun] was one of the few to survive and went nearly mad with grief as [PAWN_pronoun] saw how many had died. The city had to be abandoned, but a few years later travelers started to tell that it was now entirely covered in flowers, as if one flower sprouted for each and every victim of the plague.</VBE_Florist.baseDescription>

  <VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.title>Child of the anima tree</VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.title>
  <VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.titleShort>Psychic</VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.titleShort>
  <VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was born and raised within very close proximity to an Anima tree. [PAWN_possessive] village taught [PAWN_objective] the great importance of this tree and how to take good care of it. As a result of spending so much time with the tree, [PAWN_objective] has a very developed connection to the psychic energies of this world.</VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.baseDescription>

  <VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.title>Animatronic mechanic</VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.title>
  <VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.titleShort>Mechanic</VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.titleShort>
  <VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] use to be a mechanic who specialized in the construction of animatronics.  [PAWN_possessive] creations were often used in movie production, restaurants, theme parks and theater productions.</VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Simraised.title>Sim-raised</VBE_Simraised.title>
  <VBE_Simraised.titleShort>Sheltered</VBE_Simraised.titleShort>
  <VBE_Simraised.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a simulated environment composed of augmented reality and virtual reality elements inside a robot-tended, environmentally sealed dome. While safe and idyllic, this placid lifestyle left [PAWN_possessive] wanting something more in life.</VBE_Simraised.baseDescription>

  <VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.title>Blacksmith apprentice</VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.title>
  <VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.titleShort>Apprentice</VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.titleShort>
  <VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked under a respected blacksmith as a young apprentice. [PAWN_objective] daily duties included tending the forge, hauling supplies, and sometimes  making smaller and simpler tools.

[PAWN_objective] favourite thing to make was small daggers and wooden weapons for [PAWN_objective] fellow children, which made [PAWN_possessive] quite popular.</VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.baseDescription>

  <VBE_JuniorJeweler.title>Junior jeweler</VBE_JuniorJeweler.title>
  <VBE_JuniorJeweler.titleShort>Mineralogist</VBE_JuniorJeweler.titleShort>
  <VBE_JuniorJeweler.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated by gems and minerals as a child. [PAWN_pronoun] built a collection, learned how to polish and cut stones, and developed an encyclopedic knowledge on mineralogy.</VBE_JuniorJeweler.baseDescription>

  <VBE_Jeweler.title>Jeweler</VBE_Jeweler.title>
  <VBE_Jeweler.titleShort>Jeweler</VBE_Jeweler.titleShort>
  <VBE_Jeweler.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] inspected, cut, polished, and sold all sorts of gems and exotic minerals. [PAWN_pronoun] could tell you the difference between ten types of quartz by lustre alone.</VBE_Jeweler.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>