<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: gravjumper engine -->
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>двигатель гравипрыжкового корабля</VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>
  <!-- EN: A compact gravtech engine designed for short-range jumps within a planet’s atmosphere. The gravjumper engine creates a brief, localized distortion in gravitational flow, allowing rapid vertical lift, but does not produce forward thrust. It can't function far from a large gravity well like a planet, so it is useless for interplanetary travel.\n\nWhen launched, anything on substructure that's connected to the grav engine will be transported to a new map.\n\nOften used by explorers, scouts, and smugglers, gravjumper engines are prized for their agility and minimal power requirements. They are simpler to produce than full gravship engines, but still rely on high-grade materials and advanced fabrication. -->
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>Компактный гравитехнологический двигатель, разработанный для коротких прыжков в атмосфере планеты. Двигатель гравипрыжкового корабля создаёт кратковременное локализованное искажение гравитационного потока, обеспечивая быстрый вертикальный подъём, но не создаёт горизонтальную тягу. Не может работать вдали от крупного гравитационного колодца вроде планеты, поэтому бесполезен для межпланетных путешествий.\n\nПри запуске всё на надстройке, соединённой с гравидвигателем, будет перемещено на новую карту.\n\nЧасто используется исследователями, разведчиками и контрабандистами; ценится за манёвренность и минимальное энергопотребление. Проще в производстве, чем полноценные гравидвигатели, но всё ещё требует высококачественных материалов и передового производства.</VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>

  <!-- EN: gravhulk engine -->
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>двигатель гравибаржи</VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>
  <!-- EN: The gravhulk is a colossal class of gravship, engineered to transport entire megacolonies, orbital platforms, or mobile city-cores across the skies of a planet. The grav engine generates lift by inverting and intensifying the effect of gravity in a field around itself. This engine can lift upwards, but does not produce forward thrust. It can't function far from a large gravity well like a planet, so it is useless for interplanetary travel.\n\nWhen launched, anything on substructure that's connected to the grav engine will be transported to a new map.\n\nGravhulks are the pride of glitterworld infrastructure fleets, often used to deploy prefabricated settlements, floating arcologies, or deep-strata excavation hubs. Their sheer scale demands enormous production facilities and crew specialization, making them one of the rarest and most powerful gravships ever built. -->
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>Гравибаржы колоссальные гравикорбали, спроектированные для транспортировки целых мегаколоний, орбитальных платформ или мобильных городских ядер по небу планеты. Гравидвигатель создаёт подъёмную силу, инвертируя и усиливая эффект гравитации в поле вокруг себя. Этот двигатель может поднимать вверх, но не создаёт горизонтальную тягу. Не может работать вдали от крупного гравитационного колодца вроде планеты, поэтому бесполезен для межпланетных путешествий.\n\nПри запуске всё на надстройке, соединённой с гравидвигателем, будет перемещено на новую карту.\n\nГравибаржи являются гордостью инфраструктурных флотов утопических миров и часто используются для развёртывания сборных поселений, летающих аркологий или глубинных раскопочных центров. Их масштаб требует огромных производственных мощностей и высокой квалификации экипажа, что делает их одними из редчайших и мощнейших гравикораблей из когда-либо построенных.</VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>
</LanguageData>