<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN:     
    <li>questName->Supersoldier lab</li> 
  -->
  <VQE_AncientLabComplex.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Лаборатория суперсолдат</li>
  </VQE_AncientLabComplex.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:     
    <li>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] of [asker_faction_name], has intercepted a mysterious broadcast. The signal carries encryption markers associated with an ancient military supersoldier program, and appears to have been transmitted from a site not far from our colony. \n\n[asker_nameDef] believes that tracking this signal will reveal the location of a hidden installation. On arrival, scouts reported finding a small, abandoned surface outpost with an open vault entrance leading deep underground.\n\nBeneath lies a sealed laboratory complex. Inside must be some kind of ancient broadcasting station - intercepting the signal from it will allow us to trace its destination. \n\nThe underground vault also contains something invaluable: an intact Archogen Injector. This rare device can be used to begin creating supersoldiers by injecting archites directly into human subjects. The injector, along with any other surviving lab equipment, should be claimed and brought back to the colony. \n\nThe lab itself shows no active defenders, but ancient traps may still be functional and must be navigated with care.</li>
    <li>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->We've intercepted an unstable remote broadcast, requesting reinforcements for some unknown event. While seemingly not intended for us, the signal appears to originate from a laboratory responsible for producing ancient supersoldiers. \n\nThe site must contain the broadcasting station responsible for the message. It is imperative that we intercept the broadcast on-site, to track where it is broadcasting to. \n\nThis trek might be dangerous, as we have no way of knowing what lies at the site. Remaining technology at the site could prove useful, we should look at each piece of equipment carefully to take back with us if we dream of creating supersoldiers of our own.</li> 
  -->
  <VQE_AncientLabComplex.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] фракции [asker_faction_name], [asker_discovered] таинственную радиопередачу. Сигнал содержит метки шифрования, связанные с древней военной программой суперсолдат, и, судя по всему, передан с объекта недалеко от нашего поселения.\n\n[asker_nameDef] посчитал, что обнаружение источника этого сигнала раскроет местоположение скрытой установки. По прибытии разведчики сообщили об обнаружении небольшого заброшенного наземного аванпоста с открытым входом в убежище, ведущим глубоко под землю.\n\nВнизу находится запечатанный лабораторный комплекс. Внутри должна быть какая-то древняя радиостанция — перехват сигнала которой позволит нам отследить его получателя.\n\nВ подземном убежище также находится нечто крайне ценное: нетронутый архогенный инъектор. Это редкое устройство можно использовать для создания суперсолдат путём прямого введения архитов подопытным. Инъектор вместе с любым другим уцелевшим лабораторным оборудованием следует забрать и доставить в поселение.\n\nВ самой лаборатории нет действующих защитников, но древние ловушки могут всё ещё функционировать, поэтому стоит соблюдать с осторожность.</li>
    <li>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->Мы перехватили нестабильную удалённую передачу, запрашивающую подкрепление для какого-то неизвестного происшествия. Хотя сигнал явно не предназначался для нас, он, похоже, исходит от лаборатории, ответственной за производство древних суперсолдат.\n\nНа объекте должна находиться радиостанция, ответственная передающая это сообщение. Крайне важно перехватить передачу на месте, чтобы отследить, куда она транслируется.\n\nЭтот путь может оказаться опасным, поскольку мы не имеем понятия, что нас ждёт на объекте. Оставшиеся там технологии могут оказаться полезными, нам следует внимательно осмотреть каждую единицу оборудования и забрать с собой, если мы мечтаем создавать собственных суперсолдат.</li>
  </VQE_AncientLabComplex.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
</LanguageData>