<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN:         
    <li>questName(priority=1)->E352 - [verb] the seized [place]</li>
    <li>verb->Secure</li>
    <li>verb->Contain</li>
    <li>verb->Unseal</li>
    <li>place->lab</li>      
    <li>place->vault</li>
    <li>place->site</li>
  -->
  <VQE_AncientResearchVault.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName(priority=1)->E352 - [verb] [place]</li>
    <li>verb->Зачистить</li>
    <li>verb->Проверить</li>
    <li>verb->Открыть</li>
    <li>place->лабораторию</li>      
    <li>place->убежище</li>
    <li>place->базу</li>
  </VQE_AncientResearchVault.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN:         
    <li>questDescription->Your radio lights up with another request for E352. The automated satellite tells you of another vault, lurking somewhere in the distance. This vault is marked one of many in a series of "seized vaults", where supersoldier patients sealed off the genetic monstrosities underground. \n\nThe site briefing attatched reads as follows:\n[story]\n\n The satellite wants you to take care of the supersoldiers, then reopen the vault door. It refuses to elaborate on what the purpose of the mission is. Your only directive is to re-open the underground section of the vault. Once it has been unsealed, you may leave or loot the site for ancient technology.</li>
    <li>story->This vault's patients guard the exterior, after they heard rumors of letting the monstrosities roam free. Afraid for their descendants, they staged an uprising to stop the entire operation. They took out several doctors then rushed to seal the massive underground vault door. After some deliberation, a group of patients decided to remain at the site. Choosing to give their lives to ensure their captors don't return to unleash the horrors onto the world was their way of keeping their families safe.</li>
    <li>story->This vault contained a cult born from captivity. Through an experiment, a patient gained a powerful ability based around the external manipulation of the inner-self. He took it upon himself to thrust his ideology onto the other patients, until a unity of intention formed among the captives. They were to seize this site for themselves, and guard it as a beacon to their new leader. Executives heard this rumor, and chose to capture him. Strapped to machines, they numbed his synapses and attempted to remove his ability with experimental treatments. As the cult burst out of containment and stormed the halls, they were unaware of the state of their leader as they mercilessly took revenge on their captors. After escaping the underground vault, the members sealed the door and stood to guard their temple. It remains unclear whether the leader managed to escape, or became a monstrosity himself in their process of detainment.</li>
    <li>story->Those who surround the vault guard a terrible secret. A patient was given the remarkable ability of telepathy through an experiment. The doctors were shocked as the man divulged specific details about their private lives. After being placed with the other patients, it is said the telepath began to disturb them with his accuracy. He began to unearth intimate details about their personal affairs, and the secrets they kept buried. Things changed when he looked at a disheveled patient for too long and heard a piece of information too dark to bear. The patients arranged to have the telepath killed, but executives intervened. The telepath used that opportunity to read the layout of the vault from one of the doctor's thoughts, and unseal the vault door. As he and a handful of other patients reached the surface, the disheveled man kicked the telepath back downstairs into the vault. Him and the other patients agreed to keep him sealed there forever, guarding their buried secrets with the horrors underneath.</li>
    <li>story->This vault is guarded by a loyal group of friends. The underground halls once contained a gifted patient with the ability to manipulate her form. She could transform into anything on a whim. The doctors would bring out turtles and rabbits to test her skill, and through a painful melting process she was able to form a shell and become unmistakably a turtle. Overtime, this process became too grueling to tolerate. She was well-liked among the other patients, and they ended up taking great pity on her. On one night, they convinced the girl to melt into the form of a doctor to stage a breakout. She managed to bring all her friends to the vault door in her disguise, but was said to have instead accidentally unleashed a wave of the failed genetic horrors. The group of patients managed to escape, but the girl was left behind. Her friends now camp above the vault, hoping to one day rescue her from the depths. They speculate that the only way she could have survived is if she assumed the form of one of the monstrosities, forced to roam the halls masquerading as one of them.</li>
  -->
  <VQE_AncientResearchVault.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Ваша радиостанция снова загорается новым запросом для E352. Автоматический спутник сообщает вам о ещё одном убежище, скрытом где-то далеко. Это убежище помечено как одно из многих в категории «захвачено», где подопытные суперсолдаты сдерживают генетические мутантов под землёй.\n\nПрилагаемая сводка по объекту гласит:\n[story]\n\nСпутник хочет, чтобы вы разобрались с суперсолдатами, а затем открыли дверь убежища. Он отказывается уточнять цель миссии. Ваша единственная задача — открыть подземную секцию убежища. После того как она будет вскрыта, вы можете покинуть место или разграбить его в поисках древних технологий.</li>
    <li>story->Подопытные этого убежища охраняют вход снаружи после того, как услышали слухи об освобождении мутантов. Боясь за своих собратьев по несчастью, они устроили восстание, чтобы остановить эксперименты. Они убили нескольких врачей, а затем бросились запечатывать массивную подземную дверь убежища. После некоторых раздумий группа подопытных решила остаться на месте. Чтобы сохранить свои семьи в безопасности они решили отдать свои жизни за то, чтобы похитители не вернулись и не выпустили ужасы в мир.</li>
    <li>story->Это убежище содержало культ, рождённый в неволе. В ходе эксперимента один подопытный получил мощную способность, основанную на нематериальном контроле. Он начал навязывать свою идеологию другим подопытным, пока среди пленников не сформировалось единство взглядов. Они должны были захватить это место и защищать его как маяк своему новому лидеру. Руководство узнало об этом и решило пленить лидера. Привязав к машинам, они заблокировали его синапсы и попытались избавиться от способности экспериментальными методами. Когда культисты вырвались из изоляции и штурмовали коридоры, они не знали о состоянии своего лидера, беспощадно мстя похитителям. Сбежав из подземного убежища, члены культа запечатали дверь и встали охранять свой храм. До сих пор неясно, удалось ли лидеру сбежать или он уже стал монстром.</li>
    <li>story->Те, кто окружает убежище, хранят ужасную тайну. В ходе эксперимента один подопытный получил удивительную способность к телепатии. Врачи были шокированы, когда человек раскрыл конкретные детали их личной жизни. После помещения к другим подопытным, говорят, телепат начал доставлять неудобства своей способностью. Он раскрывал слишком личные подробности их жизни и секреты, которые они хранили в тайне. Но всё изменилось, когда он слишком долго смотрел на одного потрёпанного пациента и узнал информацию слишком тёмную, чтобы её вынести. Подопытные договорились убить телепата, но вмешалось руководство. Телепат воспользовался этой возможностью, чтобы считать планировку убежища из мыслей одного из врачей и открыть дверь убежища. Когда он и горстка других подопытных достигли поверхности, потрёпанный человек пнул телепата обратно вниз в убежище. Он и остальные подопытные договорились держать его там навечно, охраняя свои погребённые секреты вместе с ужасами внизу.</li>
    <li>story->Это убежище охраняет преданная группа друзей. В подземных залах когда-то содержалась одарённая подопытная со способностью изменять собственную форму. Она могла превращаться во что угодно по желанию. Врачи приносили черепах и кроликов, чтобы проверить её навыки, и через болезненный процесс трансформации она могла сформировать панцирь и стать безошибочно черепахой. Со временем этот процесс стал слишком мучительным, чтобы терпеть. Её любили среди других подопытных, и они очень сжалились над ней. Однажды ночью они убедили девушку принять форму врача, чтобы устроить побег. Ей удалось вывести всех своих друзей к двери убежища благодаря маскировке, но в конце она сказала, что случайно выпустила волну неудачных генетических мутантов и их нужно сдержать. Группе удалось сбежать, но девушка осталась позади. Её друзья теперь разбили лагерь над убежищем, надеясь однажды спасти её из глубин. Они предполагают, что единственный способ, которым мог позволить ей выжить — принять форму одного из мутантов. И теперь она вынуждена бродить по залам, притворяясь одним из них.</li>
  </VQE_AncientResearchVault.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
</LanguageData>