<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EN: 
    questName->Cryptoforge bow
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName-&gt;Cryptoforge bow</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: 
    questDescription->Data recovered from the ancient relay station has revealed the crash site of the cryptoforge ship’s bow, located not far from the scanning relay’s position. While this section does not house the cryptoforge itself, it contains a vital black box. To locate the final ship fragment, we must retrieve its data and pair it with the information from the stern’s black box. \n\nScans indicate a significant presence of insectoid lifeforms infesting the wreckage, making combat inevitable if we wish to reach the bridge where the black box is stored. The ship’s hull is composed of nearly indestructible material, limiting our means of entry. Some ancient airlocks may still function, but forcing them open will be necessary. A weak energy signature has also been detected within - likely from a dormant reactor. If reactivated, it may power the ship’s old floor heaters, weakening the cold-adapted insectoids inside.\n\nAlthough the cryptoforge itself is not housed within this wreckage, valuable resources remain, fused and reshaped by the ship’s violent descent. Extracting these materials will aid in restoring the cryptoforge and crafting the legendary cryptogear. Studying the black box should be our top priority.
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription-&gt;Data recovered from the ancient relay station has revealed the crash site of the cryptoforge ship’s bow, located not far from the scanning relay’s position. While this section does not house the cryptoforge itself, it contains a vital black box. To locate the final ship fragment, we must retrieve its data and pair it with the information from the stern’s black box. \n\nScans indicate a significant presence of insectoid lifeforms infesting the wreckage, making combat inevitable if we wish to reach the bridge where the black box is stored. The ship’s hull is composed of nearly indestructible material, limiting our means of entry. Some ancient airlocks may still function, but forcing them open will be necessary. A weak energy signature has also been detected within - likely from a dormant reactor. If reactivated, it may power the ship’s old floor heaters, weakening the cold-adapted insectoids inside.\n\nAlthough the cryptoforge itself is not housed within this wreckage, valuable resources remain, fused and reshaped by the ship’s violent descent. Extracting these materials will aid in restoring the cryptoforge and crafting the legendary cryptogear. Studying the black box should be our top priority.</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

</LanguageData>