<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EN: 
    questName->Cryptoforge bow
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Нос криптокузницы</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: 
    questDescription->Data recovered from the ancient relay station has revealed the crash site of the cryptoforge ship’s bow, located not far from the scanning relay’s position. While this section does not house the cryptoforge itself, it contains a vital black box. To locate the final ship fragment, we must retrieve its data and pair it with the information from the stern’s black box. \n\nScans indicate a significant presence of insectoid lifeforms infesting the wreckage, making combat inevitable if we wish to reach the bridge where the black box is stored. The ship’s hull is composed of nearly indestructible material, limiting our means of entry. Some ancient airlocks may still function, but forcing them open will be necessary. A weak energy signature has also been detected within - likely from a dormant reactor. If reactivated, it may power the ship’s old floor heaters, weakening the cold-adapted insectoids inside.\n\nAlthough the cryptoforge itself is not housed within this wreckage, valuable resources remain, fused and reshaped by the ship’s violent descent. Extracting these materials will aid in restoring the cryptoforge and crafting the legendary cryptogear. Studying the black box should be our top priority.
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Данные, извлечённые с древней станции ретрансляторов, раскрыли местоположение места крушения носа корабля-криптокузницы, расположенного недалеко от позиции сканирующего ретранслятора. Хотя в этой секции не находится сама криптокузница, она содержит жизненно важный чёрный ящик. Чтобы найти финальный обломок корабля, мы должны извлечь его данные и соединить их с информацией из чёрного ящика кормы.\n\nСканирование показывает значительное присутствие инсектоидных форм жизни, заселивших обломки, что делает бой неизбежным, если мы хотим добраться до мостика, где хранится чёрный ящик. Корпус корабля состоит из практически неразрушимого материала, ограничивая наши способы проникновения. Некоторые древние шлюзы могут всё ещё функционировать, но их придётся принудительно вскрывать. Внутри также обнаружена слабая энергетическая сигнатура — вероятно, от спящего реактора. Если его реактивировать, он может питать старые напольные обогреватели корабля, ослабляя адаптированных к холоду инсектоидов внутри.\n\nХотя сама криптокузница не размещена в этих обломках, ценные ресурсы остались, сплавленные и переформированные жестоким падением корабля. Извлечение этих материалов поможет в восстановлении криптокузницы и изготовлении легендарного криптоснаряжения. Изучение чёрного ящика должно быть нашим главным приоритетом.</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter3.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

</LanguageData>