<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EN: 
    questName->Scanning for the Cryptoforge
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Поиск Криптокузницы</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: 
    questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] of [asker_faction_name], has contacted us with news of a long-lost starship. Generations ago, a legendary vessel belonging to a nomadic warrior fleet crashed on this planet, its crew renowned for wielding cryptoparticles in battle. The cryptoforge ship shattered upon atmospheric entry, breaking into three massive fragments scattered across the surface. To locate them, we must reactivate an ancient scanning relay station. \n\n[asker_nameDef] says that initiating the scans will allow us to pinpoint the locations of the ship’s stern and bow, which may hold further clues to the whereabouts of the final, most crucial fragment. However, the relay station remains heavily secured - automated turrets still stand watch, and the surrounding grounds are riddled with a dense minefield. Worse yet, the power surge from the scan is certain to draw the attention of nearby mechanoids.\n\nComplete the scans on both relays to discover the location of the ship fragments.
    questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->We’ve uncovered information about a long-lost starship. Generations ago, a legendary vessel belonging to a nomadic warrior fleet crashed on this planet, its crew renowned for wielding cryptoparticles in battle. The cryptoforge ship shattered upon atmospheric entry, breaking into three massive fragments scattered across the surface. To locate them, we must reactivate an ancient scanning relay station. \n\nInitiating the scans will allow us to pinpoint the locations of the ship’s stern and bow, which may hold further clues to the whereabouts of the final, most crucial fragment. However, the relay station remains heavily secured - automated turrets still stand watch, and the surrounding grounds are riddled with a dense minefield. Worse yet, the power surge from the scan is certain to draw the attention of nearby mechanoids.\n\nComplete the scans on both relays to discover the location of the ship fragments.
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] фракции [asker_faction_name], связался с нами с новостями о давно утраченном звездолёте. Поколения назад легендарный корабль, принадлежащий кочевому флоту воинов, потерпел крушение на этой планете — его экипаж славился мастерством владения крипточастицами в бою. Корабль-криптокузница разрушился при входе в атмосферу, распавшись на три массивных обломка, разбросанных по поверхности. Чтобы найти их, мы должны реактивировать древнюю станцию сканирующих ретрансляторов.\n\n[asker_nameDef] говорит, что запуск сканирования позволит нам точно определить местоположение кормы и носа корабля, которые могут содержать дополнительные подсказки о местонахождении финального, наиболее важного обломка. Однако станция ретрансляторов остаётся сильно защищённой — автоматические турели всё ещё несут вахту, а окружающая территория нашпигована плотным минным полем. Хуже того, энергетический всплеск от сканирования наверняка привлечёт внимание ближайших механоидов.\n\nЗавершите сканирование на обеих станциях, чтобы обнаружить местоположение обломков корабля.</li>
    <li>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->Мы обнаружили информацию о давно утраченном звездолёте. Поколения назад легендарный корабль, принадлежащий кочевому флоту воинов, потерпел крушение на этой планете — его экипаж славился мастерством владения крипточастицами в бою. Корабль-криптокузница разрушился при входе в атмосферу, распавшись на три массивных обломка, разбросанных по поверхности. Чтобы найти их, мы должны реактивировать древнюю станцию сканирующих ретрансляторов.\n\nЗапуск сканирования позволит нам точно определить местоположение кормы и носа корабля, которые могут содержать дополнительные подсказки о местонахождении финального, наиболее важного обломка. Однако станция ретрансляторов остаётся сильно защищённой — автоматические турели всё ещё несут вахту, а окружающая территория нашпигована плотным минным полем. Хуже того, энергетический всплеск от сканирования наверняка привлечёт внимание ближайших механоидов.\n\nЗавершите сканирование на обеих станциях, чтобы обнаружить местоположение обломков корабля.</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

</LanguageData>