<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EN: 
    questName->Legendary cryptoforge
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter4.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Легендарная криптокузница</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter4.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: 
    questDescription->After analyzing the data from both black boxes, we have finally pinpointed the location of the last ship fragment - home to the legendary cryptoforge. This ancient ultratech workshop contains the lost knowledge and equipment necessary to craft cryptogear, a technology long thought to be impossible to recreate by any other means. This is our only chance to forge such items, so we must bring our best crafters and as many resources as possible.\n\nThe cryptoforge requires an immense amount of power to function, but the crash site still contains a dormant cryptogenerator. While it survived the descent, it only has enough fuel to run for 48 hours. Once activated, it will begin a countdown to meltdown, wiping the entire fragment from the planet’s surface, along with the cryptoforge. This limited time frame means we must work quickly, crafting as much cryptogear as possible before the generator’s collapse. Enabling the cryptogenerator will also reactivate the ship’s ancient defensive turrets, providing much-needed protection against the mechanoids that will inevitably arrive, drawn to the massive energy surge.\n\nBeyond the cryptoforge, the ship’s interior appears remarkably intact. The sealed structure has preserved valuable resources, food, and medicine, as well as functional sleeping quarters, a recreation area, and other remnants of cryptoforge technology. The environment will still be harsh, but the cryptogenerator will power the ship’s heaters and lights, making the space more suitable for extended work. One cryptosleep casket remains occupied, whoever is inside has been frozen for centuries. Freeing them could prove useful, though it is not essential to our mission.\n\nThis is our one and only opportunity. Once the generator melts down, the cryptoforge and its secrets will be lost forever. We must establish a strong defense, make the most of our limited time, and craft as much legendary cryptogear as possible before the clock runs out.
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter4.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->После анализа данных с обоих чёрных ящиков мы наконец точно определили местоположение последнего обломка корабля — дома легендарной криптокузницы. Эта древняя ультратех-мастерская содержит утраченные знания и оборудование, необходимые для изготовления криптоснаряжения — технологии, которую долго считали невозможной для воссоздания любыми другими средствами. Это наш единственный шанс изготовить такие предметы, поэтому мы должны взять лучших ремесленников и как можно больше ресурсов.\n\nКриптокузница требует огромного количества энергии для работы, но место крушения всё ещё содержит неактивный криптогенератор. Хотя он выжил при падении, у него достаточно топлива для работы только на 48 часов. После активации начнётся обратный отсчёт до расплавления, которое сотрёт весь обломок с поверхности планеты вместе с криптокузницей. Это ограниченное время означает, что мы должны работать быстро, изготавливая как можно больше криптоснаряжения до разрушения генератора. Включение криптогенератора также реактивирует древние защитные турели корабля, обеспечивая столь необходимую защиту от механоидов, которые неизбежно прибудут, привлечённые мощным энергетическим всплеском.\n\nПомимо криптокузницы, внутренняя часть корабля выглядит удивительно нетронутой. Герметичная структура сохранила ценные ресурсы, еду и лекарства, а также функциональные спальные помещения, зону отдыха и другие остатки криптокузнечных технологий. Среда всё ещё будет суровой, но криптогенератор обеспечит питанием обогреватели и освещение корабля, делая пространство более подходящим для длительной работы. Одна криптосонная капсула остаётся занятой — кто бы ни находился внутри, он был заморожен столетиями. Освобождение может оказаться полезным, хотя это и не является обязательным для нашей миссии.\n\nЭто наша единственная и неповторимая возможность. Как только генератор расплавится, криптокузница и её секреты будут потеряны навсегда. Мы должны установить сильную оборону, максимально использовать ограниченное время и изготовить как можно больше легендарного криптоснаряжения, пока время не истекло.</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter4.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

</LanguageData>