<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: 
    <li>questName->Scanning for the Cryptoforge</li>
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Поиск Криптокузницы</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: 
    <li>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] of [asker_faction_name], has contacted us with news of a long-lost starship. Generations ago, a legendary vessel belonging to a nomadic warrior fleet crashed on this planet, its crew renowned for wielding cryptoparticles in battle. The cryptoforge ship shattered upon atmospheric entry, breaking into three massive fragments scattered across the surface. To locate them, we must reactivate an ancient scanning relay station. \n\n[asker_nameDef] says that initiating the scans will allow us to pinpoint the locations of the ship’s stern and bow, which may hold further clues to the whereabouts of the final, most crucial fragment. However, the relay station remains heavily secured - automated turrets still stand watch, and the surrounding grounds are riddled with a dense minefield. Worse yet, the power surge from the scan is certain to draw the attention of nearby mechanoids.\n\nComplete the scans on both relays to discover the location of the ship fragments.</li>
    <li>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->We’ve uncovered information about a long-lost starship. Generations ago, a legendary vessel belonging to a nomadic warrior fleet crashed on this planet, its crew renowned for wielding cryptoparticles in battle. The cryptoforge ship shattered upon atmospheric entry, breaking into three massive fragments scattered across the surface. To locate them, we must reactivate an ancient scanning relay station. \n\nInitiating the scans will allow us to pinpoint the locations of the ship’s stern and bow, which may hold further clues to the whereabouts of the final, most crucial fragment. However, the relay station remains heavily secured - automated turrets still stand watch, and the surrounding grounds are riddled with a dense minefield. Worse yet, the power surge from the scan is certain to draw the attention of nearby mechanoids.\n\nComplete the scans on both relays to discover the location of the ship fragments.</li>
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] фракции [asker_faction_name], сообщает о давно утраченном звездолёте. Поколения назад легендарный корабль, принадлежавший кочевому флоту воинов, потерпел крушение на этой планете — его экипаж славился умением использовать крипточастицы в бою. Корабль-криптокузница развалился при входе в атмосферу, распавшись на три огромных обломка, разбросанных по поверхности. Чтобы отыскать их, нужно вновь активировать древнюю сканирующую ретрансляционную станцию.\n\n[asker_nameDef] утверждает, что запуск сканирования позволит точно определить координаты носовой и кормовой секций, которые могут содержать подсказки о местонахождении последнего, ключевого сегмента. Но станция всё ещё серьёзно защищена — автоматические турели продолжают дежурство, а окружающая территория нашпигована плотным минным полем. Хуже того, энергетический всплеск сканирования почти наверняка привлечёт внимание ближайших механоидов.\n\nАктивируйте оба ретранслятора и завершите сканирование, чтобы выявить расположение обломков.</li>
    <li>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->Мы обнаружили сведения о давно утраченном звездолёте. Поколения назад легендарный корабль кочевого воинского флота разбился на этой планете — его экипаж был знаменит применением крипточастиц в бою. Корабль-криптокузница разломился в атмосфере и распался на три крупных сегмента, раскиданных по поверхности. Чтобы обнаружить их, потребуется вновь активировать древнюю сканирующую ретрансляционную станцию.\n\nЗапуск сканирования позволит точно определить координаты кормовой и носовой секций, которые могут указать путь к последнему, наиболее важному фрагменту. Однако станция остаётся укреплённой — автоматические турели всё ещё активны, а периметр густо усеян минами. Хуже того, энергетический импульс сканирования почти наверняка привлечёт внимание близлежащих механоидов.\n\nАктивируйте оба ретранслятора и завершите сканирование, чтобы установить местоположение обломков.</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
</LanguageData>