<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EN: 
    questName->Cryptoforge stern
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Корма криптокузницы</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: 
    questDescription->Data retrieved from the ancient relay station confirms the crash site of the cryptoforge ship’s stern, located not far from the scanning facility. While this section does not contain the legendary cryptoforge itself, it holds a crucial black box. To pinpoint the final cryptoforge fragment, we must retrieve its data and pair it with the bow’s black box records. \n\nThe wreckage scan reveals a high concentration of dormant mechanoids aboard, making conflict likely. The ship’s hull is built from near-indestructible material, limiting possible entry points. Ancient airlocks might still be operational, though forcing them open will require effort. Some external turrets remain active, further complicating the approach. Inside, automated floor freezers keep the corridors at dangerously low temperatures, serving as a defensive measure against intruders. \n\nDespite these challenges, the wreckage contains valuable resources. Extracting as much salvage as possible will be essential for reactivating the cryptoforge and crafting the legendary cryptogear.\n\nAccording to the scan, the ship is protected by at least:\n[ListOfEnemies]
   -->
	<VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Данные, извлечённые с древней станции ретрансляторов, подтверждают местоположение места крушения кормы корабля-криптокузницы, расположенного недалеко от сканирующего объекта. Хотя в этой секции не находится сама легендарная криптокузница, она содержит важнейший чёрный ящик. Чтобы точно определить местоположение финального обломка криптокузницы, мы должны извлечь его данные и соединить их с записями чёрного ящика носа.\n\nСканирование обломков показывает высокую концентрацию спящих механоидов на борту, что делает конфликт вероятным. Корпус корабля построен из практически неразрушимого материала, ограничивая возможные точки входа. Древние шлюзы могут всё ещё функционировать, хотя их принудительное вскрытие потребует усилий. Некоторые внешние турели остаются активными, ещё больше осложняя приближение. Внутри автоматические напольные морозильники поддерживают в коридорах опасно низкие температуры, служа защитной мерой против вторжений.\n\nНесмотря на эти трудности, обломки содержат ценные ресурсы. Извлечение максимально возможного количества материалов будет критически важным для реактивации криптокузницы и изготовления легендарного криптоснаряжения.\n\nСогласно сканированию, корабль защищён как минимум:\n[ListOfEnemies]</li>
  </VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter2.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

</LanguageData>