<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Quests Expanded - Drone Factory</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson, Taranchuk, Ferny</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
	
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>

	<packageId>vanillaquestsexpanded.dronefactory</packageId>
	<description>In the Drone Factory mod, players are thrust into a rust-choked industrial conflict as the planet’s dormant war machines mysteriously blink back to life. The escalating crisis begins with expeditions into derelict drone scrapyards - valuable but perilous dens of discarded military hardware. Here, colonists must dismantle erratic, half-functional defenders to scavenge fragmented command cores and proprietary blueprints once thought lost to time.

However, the threat quickly reaches your doorstep when a rogue long-range transmitter begins broadcasting an awakening signal across the region. As relentless waves of vagrant drones besiege your settlement, your caravan must mount a strike against an abandoned robotics warehouse to silence the long range transmitter and stop the awakened drones.

Tracing the origin of these rogue broadcasts leads to the campaign's grand finale: a massive, ancient factory repurposed by a powerful pirate gang. These raiders are mass-producing drones for a lucrative black market, guided by a captive genius known only as The Tinkerer. During the siege, your forces must breach the factory's heavy fortifications, battling a lethal combination of seasoned pirates and fresh, off-the-line drone defenders that are continuously manufactured during your approach.

In the heart of the facility, a critical choice awaits: rescue The Tinkerer from captivity to fully unlock his ancient knowledge, or eliminate him to ensure the blueprints never fall into the wrong hands again.

The emergence of the drones allows your colony to reverse-engineer the technology, giving you the ability to construct your own mechanized workforce: a tireless, automated industrial constructs and a loyal defensive force to protect your colony.</description>
</ModMetaData>
