<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: shambler apocalypse -->
	<VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.label>апокалипсис шамблеров</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.label>
  <!-- EN: Detonation of Deadlife dust warheads in the upper atmosphere has permanently altered planetary conditions. A dense death pall now blankets the world. This pall reanimates all unburied corpses exposed to the open air. -->
	<VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.description>Детонация боеголовок «Посмертия» в верхних слоях атмосферы навсегда изменила условия на планете. Плотный туман из частиц мёртвой жизни накрыл поверхность. Он возвращает к жизни все непогребённые тела, лежащие на открытом воздухе.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.description>
  <!-- EN: Most of the deadlife dust has fallen. The death pall is ending. -->
	<VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.endMessage>Большая часть частиц осела. Туман смерти рассеивается.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.endMessage>
  <!-- EN: Detonation of Deadlife dust warheads in the upper atmosphere has permanently altered planetary conditions. A dense death pall now blankets the world.\n\nThis pall reanimates all unburied corpses exposed to the open air. Any non-mechanoid corpse not under a roof will rise again as a shambler. Burned or fully destroyed corpses are unaffected.\n\nWhile the death pall is active, no normal weather transitions can occur. Rain will not fall, and fires may spread unchecked.\n\nOn a global scale, the death pall will linger for anywhere from three seasons to several years. In its wake, roaming Shambler hordes will now traverse the world, overrunning settlements and hunting down caravans. -->
	<VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.letterText>Детонация боеголовок «Посмертия» в верхних слоях атмосферы навсегда изменила условия на планете. Плотный туман из частиц мёртвой жизни накрыл поверхность.\n\nЭтот туман возвращает к жизни все непогребённые тела, лежащие на открытом воздухе. Любой труп, кроме механоидов, не находящийся под крышей, снова вернётся к жизни в качестве шамблера. Сожжённые или полностью уничтоженные трупы так же не поднимутся.\n\nПока туман смерти активен, обычная смена погоды не будет работать. Дождь не будет начинаться, а огонь сможет распространяться беспрепятственно.\n\nВ глобальном масштабе туман смерти будет держаться от трёх сезонов до нескольких лет. В это время бродячие орды шамблеров теперь будут пересекать мир, захватывая поселения и охотясь на караваны.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.letterText>
</LanguageData>