<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Muskox -->

  <AEXP_Muskox.label>musk ox</AEXP_Muskox.label>
  <AEXP_Muskox.description>Musk oxen are massive buffalo-like mammals that roam the tundra areas in search for roots, mosses and lichens to sustain them. Being related to muffalos, musk oxen can be used as pack animals. They are noted for their thick coat and for the strong odor emitted during the seasonal rut by males, from which their name derives.</AEXP_Muskox.description>
  <AEXP_Muskox.tools.0.label>head</AEXP_Muskox.tools.0.label>
  <AEXP_Muskox.tools.1.label>left hoof</AEXP_Muskox.tools.1.label>
  <AEXP_Muskox.tools.2.label>right hoof</AEXP_Muskox.tools.2.label>


  <!-- Moose -->

  <AEXP_Moose.label>moose</AEXP_Moose.label>
  <AEXP_Moose.description>The largest and heaviest member of the deer family, well-adapted to life in cold climates. Can easily be identified due to the size of the antlers and long, thin legs. Cannot carry packs, but domesticated moose can be milked. Unlike most other deer species, moose do not form herds and are solitary animals. Although generally slow-moving and sedentary, moose can become aggressive and move quickly if angered or startled.</AEXP_Moose.description>
  <AEXP_Moose.tools.0.label>left hoof</AEXP_Moose.tools.0.label>
  <AEXP_Moose.tools.1.label>right hoof</AEXP_Moose.tools.1.label>
  <AEXP_Moose.tools.3.label>head</AEXP_Moose.tools.3.label>


  <!-- Megawolverine -->

  <AEXP_MegaWolverine.label>megawolverine</AEXP_MegaWolverine.label>
  <AEXP_MegaWolverine.description>A giant, genetically-engineered predator with massive paws to rip apart prey. Thick fur allows it to survive the coldest of climates, whilst it strength allows it to hunt even the largest of mammals for food.</AEXP_MegaWolverine.description>
  <AEXP_MegaWolverine.tools.0.label>left claw</AEXP_MegaWolverine.tools.0.label>
  <AEXP_MegaWolverine.tools.1.label>right claw</AEXP_MegaWolverine.tools.1.label>
  <AEXP_MegaWolverine.tools.3.label>head</AEXP_MegaWolverine.tools.3.label>


  <!-- Porcupine -->

  <AEXP_Porcupine.label>porcupine</AEXP_Porcupine.label>
  <AEXP_Porcupine.description>A large rodent with a coat of sharp quills that protect it against predators.</AEXP_Porcupine.description>
  <AEXP_Porcupine.tools.0.label>left claw</AEXP_Porcupine.tools.0.label>
  <AEXP_Porcupine.tools.1.label>right claw</AEXP_Porcupine.tools.1.label>
  <AEXP_Porcupine.tools.3.label>head</AEXP_Porcupine.tools.3.label>


</LanguageData>