<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VQE_SalvageableDroneWreck.label>salvageable drone wreck</VQE_SalvageableDroneWreck.label>
  <VQE_SalvageableDroneWreck.description>A massive, battered section of a military drone with extreme combat damage. Though exposed wiring is visible, the valuable drone core remains sealed inside, likely intact and salvageable. If you could extract the drone core, you could decrypt it to unlock a new drone schematic. The drone's incendiary ammunition stash is intact but unstable, and will likely detonate after you do some damage.</VQE_SalvageableDroneWreck.description>

  <VQE_DroneStorageTerminal.label>drone storage terminal</VQE_DroneStorageTerminal.label>
  <VQE_DroneStorageTerminal.description>A drone storage computer terminal. It can be hacked to disable nearby dormant drones permanently.</VQE_DroneStorageTerminal.description>

  <VQE_LongRangeDroneTransmitter.label>long range drone transmitter</VQE_LongRangeDroneTransmitter.label>
  <VQE_LongRangeDroneTransmitter.description>A bulky, multi-band antenna array designed to broadcast a drone control signal over an exceptional range. The unit is currently operating, providing operational bandwidth to all nearby drones. It can be temporarily hacked to overload its internal safeguards, rendering it inert and allowing access to its valuable core.</VQE_LongRangeDroneTransmitter.description>

  <VQE_AutomatedDroneAssembler.label>automated drone assembler</VQE_AutomatedDroneAssembler.label>
  <VQE_AutomatedDroneAssembler.description>A massive, heavily armored production line dedicated to the relentless, automated assembly of drones. Complex mechanical arms work in a continuous cycle, feeding components, welding seams, and running diagnostic checks. It will continue to churn out hostile drone units until destroyed.</VQE_AutomatedDroneAssembler.description>

  <VQE_TinkererHoldingPlatform.label>tinkerer holding platform</VQE_TinkererHoldingPlatform.label>
  <VQE_TinkererHoldingPlatform.description>A specialized docking and recharge platform used for high-value, non-combat drone like the Tinkerer. Its durable construction is designed to secure and protect the drone. The platform can be destroyed to recover its resources, or it can be hacked to override its security protocols and release the Tinkerer, which will be reprogrammed to immediately join your colony.</VQE_TinkererHoldingPlatform.description>


</LanguageData>