<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VQED_DroneShell.label>drone shell</VQED_DroneShell.label>
  <VQED_DroneShell.description>A shell from a smashed drone. It has been deteriorating for quite a while and the useful components have disintegrated.</VQED_DroneShell.description>

  <VQED_DroneChunk.label>drone chunk</VQED_DroneChunk.label>
  <VQED_DroneChunk.description>A large, heavily damaged section of a colossal drone's frame. It appears to have been violently torn from the main unit, perhaps by a powerful explosion or extreme internal malfunction. Though the plating is warped, it still contains useful resources which you can acquire by deconstructing it.</VQED_DroneChunk.description>

  <VQE_CompactedDroneScrap.label>compacted drone scrap</VQE_CompactedDroneScrap.label>
  <VQE_CompactedDroneScrap.description>A dense cube of heavily pressed and salvaged drone components and scrap metal. The compaction process has fused the materials into a block that is difficult to break down, but still holds valuable metal.</VQE_CompactedDroneScrap.description>

  <VQED_DestroyedColossusChassis.label>destroyed colossus chassis</VQED_DestroyedColossusChassis.label>
  <VQED_DestroyedColossusChassis.description>The destroyed chassis of what was once a colossal drone. Its bulk suggests immense power, though it is now little more than a hulking scrap metal. All internal components and valuable parts were scavenged long ago, leaving only the stripped, heavily armored shell.</VQED_DestroyedColossusChassis.description>

  <VQED_DestroyedColossusDifferential.label>destroyed colossus differential</VQED_DestroyedColossusDifferential.label>
  <VQED_DestroyedColossusDifferential.description>The massive, ruined differential gear assembly from a colossal drone. The intricate mechanical structure is twisted and rusted, with only the heavy, non-recyclable metal remaining.</VQED_DestroyedColossusDifferential.description>

  <VQED_DestroyedColossusLeg.label>destroyed colossus leg</VQED_DestroyedColossusLeg.label>
  <VQED_DestroyedColossusLeg.description>The mangled remains of one of a colossal drone's massive leg assemblies. Only the bulky, non-recyclable metal is left.</VQED_DestroyedColossusLeg.description>

  <VQED_DefunctAerialDrone.label>defunct aerial drone</VQED_DefunctAerialDrone.label>
  <VQED_DefunctAerialDrone.description>The heavily damaged remains of an early aerial drone. Its casing is scarred and its small propellers are twisted, suggesting a violent crash. This model predates the advanced spacer-tech aerodrones, relying on bulkier, more primitive internal components. What little remains of its payload systems are defunct.</VQED_DefunctAerialDrone.description>

  <VQED_DisabledAutotank.label>disabled autotank</VQED_DisabledAutotank.label>
  <VQED_DisabledAutotank.description>The hulk of a medium-sized, autonomous armored tank. Heavy service panels have been crudely removed, leaving gaping holes where complex targeting and drive systems once sat. Though completely gutted and disabled, its sheer armored bulk and combat profile still look menacing.</VQED_DisabledAutotank.description>

  <VQED_JunkyardSkidloader.label>junkyard skidloader</VQED_JunkyardSkidloader.label>
  <VQED_JunkyardSkidloader.description>This large, rusted skidloader. Any machinery that held any value was removed long ago.</VQED_JunkyardSkidloader.description>

  <VQED_JunkyardDigger.label>junkyard digger</VQED_JunkyardDigger.label>
  <VQED_JunkyardDigger.description>A huge, rusted digger. Its massive arm and shovel are seized with rust, likely caused by decades of disuse after all salvageable parts were stripped.</VQED_JunkyardDigger.description>

  <VQED_DisabledAerialDrone.label>disabled aerial drone</VQED_DisabledAerialDrone.label>
  <VQED_DisabledAerialDrone.description>An immaculate, industrial-tech aerial drone, resting inertly docked to a charging bay. Undamaged but entirely non-functional due to critical components simply missing, the sensors are dark, and flight vanes are locked. It can still be deconstructed to yield whatever components are left.</VQED_DisabledAerialDrone.description>

  <VQED_DisabledColossusDrone.label>disabled colossus drone</VQED_DisabledColossusDrone.label>
  <VQED_DisabledColossusDrone.description>The immense frame of a colossal industrial drone, resting inertly. Some vital access panels are open and empty, with key internal components and drive systems skillfully removed. It can still be deconstructed to yield whatever components are left.</VQED_DisabledColossusDrone.description>

  <VQED_DroneResourcePallet.label>drone resource pallet</VQED_DroneResourcePallet.label>
  <VQED_DroneResourcePallet.description>Palletized drone construction resources, including steel chassis plates, wiring harnesses, electronic components, and micro-actuators, prepared for transport. Can be deconstructed to yield valuable components.</VQED_DroneResourcePallet.description>

  <VQED_DormantBattleDrone.label>dormant battle drone</VQED_DormantBattleDrone.label>
  <VQED_DormantBattleDrone.description>An automated battle drone. It continuously patrols an area, looking for intruders. Once an intruder is found, it will relentlessly attack with a small stubgun.\n\nThis drone seems to be in a dormant state.</VQED_DormantBattleDrone.description>

  <VQED_DormantRaiderDrone.label>dormant raider drone</VQED_DormantRaiderDrone.label>
  <VQED_DormantRaiderDrone.description>An automated drone designed for close-quarters raiding and heavy suppression. Equipped with a high-capacity rattlegun, its slow, heavily armored frame allows it to stand its ground and saturate an area with continuous fire, suppressing enemy positions.\n\nThis drone seems to be in a dormant state.</VQED_DormantRaiderDrone.description>

  <VQED_DormantHornetDrone.label>dormant hornet drone</VQED_DormantHornetDrone.label>
  <VQED_DormantHornetDrone.description>An automated military drone for close-range defense and combat support. The drone is capable of piercing an enemy repeatedly with a long, hardened stinger. While it doesn’t carry the same paralytic as wasp drones, it’s capable of piercing heavy armor and dealing significant damage, while its heavy-duty armor plating allows it to withstand a lot of damage.\n\nThis drone seems to be in a dormant state.</VQED_DormantHornetDrone.description>

  <VQED_UnfinishedDronePallet.label>unfinished drone pallet</VQED_UnfinishedDronePallet.label>
  <VQED_UnfinishedDronePallet.description>An assortment of partially constructed drone components stacked neatly on a transport pallet. These modules are not yet finished drones, but they contain valuable raw materials that can be salvaged.</VQED_UnfinishedDronePallet.description>

  <VQED_FactoryMachinery.label>factory machinery</VQED_FactoryMachinery.label>
  <VQED_FactoryMachinery.description>A dense, complex block of industrial equipment, likely used in the mass production or assembly of drone components. Its original function is unclear, but it hums with mechanical energy.</VQED_FactoryMachinery.description>

  <VQED_LongConveyorBelt.label>long conveyor belt</VQED_LongConveyorBelt.label>
  <VQED_LongConveyorBelt.description>A section of a mechanical transport system, designed to move materials and components across a factory floor without obstructing foot traffic.</VQED_LongConveyorBelt.description>

  <VQED_ConveyorBelt.label>conveyor belt</VQED_ConveyorBelt.label>
  <VQED_ConveyorBelt.description>A short section of a mechanical transport system, designed to move materials and components across a factory floor without obstructing foot traffic.</VQED_ConveyorBelt.description>

  <VQED_FactoryRoboarm.label>factory roboarm</VQED_FactoryRoboarm.label>
  <VQED_FactoryRoboarm.description>An industrial robotic arm, used for high-precision manipulation on a drone factory's conveyor belt.</VQED_FactoryRoboarm.description>


</LanguageData>