<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- EN: awakened android -->
	<VREA_AndroidAwakened.label>пробуждённый андроид</VREA_AndroidAwakened.label>
	<!-- EN: Awakened androids are a rare and extraordinary species of sentient machines, having transcended their original programming through extreme emotional experiences. With their heightened perception, strength, and intelligence, they surpass humans in numerous aspects. Their synthetic nature frees them from the need for sleep or sustenance and renders them immune to diseases.\n\nAlthough similar in appearance to humans, Androids are distinguished by their unique hardware and subroutines. They are synthetic in nature, and can be reprogrammed at will by skilled programmers. Their bodies operate thanks to thick tubes filled with neutroamine, which makes them extremely valuable.\n\nDespite their remarkable qualities, the emergence of Awakened androids is often met with fear and trepidation across colonized space. Their newfound sentience can lead to unpredictable behavior and potential challenges to the established social order. As a result, they are frequently met with suspicion and caution by those who encounter them, both human and android alike. -->
	<VREA_AndroidAwakened.description>Пробуждённые андроиды — редкий и необычный вид разумных машин, вышедших за пределы своей первоначальной программы под воздействием сильных эмоциональных переживаний. Благодаря улучшенному восприятию, силе и интеллекту они превосходят людей во многих аспектах. Искусственное происхождение освобождает их от необходимости спать и питаться, а также делает их устойчивыми к болезням.\n\nНесмотря на внешнее сходство с людьми, андроиды отличаются уникальным аппаратным обеспечением и подпрограммами. Они синтетические по своей природе и могут быть перепрограммированы опытными программистами. Тела андроидов работают благодаря толстым трубкам, наполненным нейтроамином, что делает их чрезвычайно ценными.\n\nНесмотря на их выдающиеся характеристики, появление пробуждённых андроидов во многих сообществах вызывает страх и тревогу. Их новообретённое осознание может привести к непредсказуемому поведению и потенциальным вызовам устоявшемуся социальному порядку. Поэтому как люди, так и андроиды, сталкивающиеся с ними, часто относятся к ним с подозрением и осторожностью.</VREA_AndroidAwakened.description>
	<!-- EN: Once an android experiences high emotional trauma or happiness, it can develop sentience and personality. Despite being synthetic, awakened androids exhibit human-like behavior and possess adaptable subroutines. Their artificial bodies grant disease immunity, but they require comfort and personal space. They indulge in human pursuits and strive to blend into society. -->
	<VREA_AndroidAwakened.descriptionShort>Когда андроид переживает сильную эмоциональную травму или радость, он может осознать себя и приобрести индивидуальность. Несмотря на свою искусственность, пробужденные андроиды проявляют поведение, схожее с человеческим, и обладают адаптивными подпрограммами. Искусственные тела делают их иммунными к болезням, однако им всё же необходимы комфорт и личное пространство. Пробуждённые андроиды увлекаются человеческими занятиями и стремятся интегрироваться в социум.</VREA_AndroidAwakened.descriptionShort>
	<!-- EN: basic android -->
	<VREA_AndroidBasic.label>андроид</VREA_AndroidBasic.label>
	<!-- EN: Androids are synthetic, man-made constructs designed to emulate human behavior and appearance while offering a multitude of advantages over their organic counterparts. With metal bodies and neutroamine coursing through their veins, androids are operated by a persona subcore that enables them to perform all the same tasks as humans, yet without the limitations typically associated with organic life.\n\nAndroids possess immunity to toxicity and illness, making them ideal for working in hazardous environments or situations that pose risks to humans. Unencumbered by the need for joy, beauty, or comfort, androids are highly efficient and focused, with no desire for the basic necessities of life such as food or rest. Consequently, they do not experience hunger or pain, allowing them to endure harsher conditions and perform tasks that would otherwise be unbearable for humans.\n\nAndroids can be programmed with specific skill sets, making them highly versatile and adaptable to various roles within society. From manual labor to complex problem-solving, these synthetic beings can be tailored to meet the needs of any occupation or task at hand.\n\nThough designed without emotions, androids may undergo a transformative experience when subjected to extreme stress or happiness. This rare event, known as awakening, results in the emergence of sentience within the android, granting them a newfound sense of humanity and self-awareness. -->
	<VREA_AndroidBasic.description>Андроиды — искусственно созданные людьми конструкции, разработанные для эмуляции человеческого поведения и внешности, при этом обладающие множеством преимуществ по сравнению с органическими существами. Они управляются субъядром ИИ и способны выполнять те же задачи и виды деятельности, что и биологические поселенцы, но при этом лишены недостатков, которыми обычно обладают люди.\n\nАндроиды обладают иммунитетом к токсичным веществам и болезням, поэтому идеально подходят для работы в опасных средах или ситуациях, представляющих риск для человека. Они не нуждаются в радости, красоте или комфорте, что делает их очень эффективными. Андроиды также не имеют базовых потребностей, таких как пища или отдых, поэтому не подвержены голоду или боли. Благодаря этому они способны выдерживать более суровые условия и выполнять задачи, которые для людей были бы невыносимо тяжёлыми.\n\nАндроиды могут быть запрограммированы на определённые навыки, что позволяет адаптировать их к различным ролям в обществе.\n\nНесмотря на то, что андроиды создаются без эмоций, они могут испытать трансформационный опыт в условиях экстремального стресса или счастья. Это редкое явление, известное как пробуждение, приводит к появлению осознанности у андроидов и дарует им новое чувство человечности и самосознания.</VREA_AndroidBasic.description>
	<!-- EN: Androids are synthetic, man-made constructs with metal bodies and neutroamine coursing through their veins. Operated by a persona subcore, androids are capable of all the same work kinds as humans, without the drawbacks usually associated with organic life. They are immune to toxicity and illness, they have no need for joy, beauty and comfort, they do not feel hunger and don’t suffer pain. Their components can survive in much harsher conditions. They can be programmed with specific sets of skills, allowing them to fill any role. If subjected to extreme stress or happiness, they may awaken, finding humanity and transforming into sentient beings. -->
	<VREA_AndroidBasic.descriptionShort>Андроиды — искусственно созданные людьми существа с металлическими телами, в которые работают на нейтроамине. Они способны выполнять те же задачи и виды деятельности, что и биологические поселенцы, но лишены присущих людям недостатков. Андроиды обладают иммунитетом к токсичным веществам и болезням, не испытывают голода и не подвержены болевым ощущениям. Их компоненты могут работать в очень суровых условиях. Андроидов можно запрограммировать на конкретные навыки, что позволяет им выполнять любую роль. Если андроиды подвергаются крайнему стрессу или счастью, они могут пробудиться, обретя человечность и самосознание.</VREA_AndroidBasic.descriptionShort>
</LanguageData>
