<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Shooting.label>shooting curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Shooting.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Shooting.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Shooting which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Shooting completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Shooting.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Melee.label>melee curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Melee.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Melee.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Melee which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Melee completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Melee.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Construction.label>construction curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Construction.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Construction.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Construction which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Construction completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Construction.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Mining.label>mining curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Mining.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Mining.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Mining which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Mining completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Mining.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Cooking.label>cooking curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Cooking.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Cooking.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Cooking which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Cooking completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Cooking.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Plants.label>plants curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Plants.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Plants.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Plants which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Plants completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Plants.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Animals.label>animals curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Animals.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Animals.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Animals which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Animals completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Animals.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Crafting.label>crafting curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Crafting.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Crafting.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Crafting which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Crafting completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Crafting.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Artistic.label>artistic curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Artistic.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Artistic.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Artistic which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Artistic completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Artistic.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Medicine.label>medicine curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Medicine.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Medicine.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Medicine which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Medical completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Medicine.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Social.label>social curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Social.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Social.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Social which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Social completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Social.description>

  <VRE_Curiosity_Intellectual.label>intellectual curiosity</VRE_Curiosity_Intellectual.label>
  <VRE_Curiosity_Intellectual.description>The carrier has a natural curiosity for Intellectual which makes them gain recreation whenever they learn it. Furthermore, curiosity prevents skill loss in Intellectual completely. 
		</VRE_Curiosity_Intellectual.description>


</LanguageData>