<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Weapons Expanded - Coilguns</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, AveryTheKitty, Taranchuk</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VWEC</packageId>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<description>Vanilla Weapons Expanded - Coilguns is an addition to one of the most popular mods of Vanilla Expanded collection - Vanilla Weapons Expanded, however it can be played without it. This mod adds a selection of spacer-tech weapons, fully craftable upon researching mass drivers technology. Coilguns come with a unique gimmick - whilst their firing speed and aiming time are quite unforgiving, projectiles fires from these weapons pierce any target they hit - flesh or metal, as well as any obstacles. Each obstacle reduces damage dealt to the next unlucky object/creature, but effectively these weapons allow your colonists to score multi-kills with a single shot.

Shots fired by these weapons cannot penetrate mountains or reinforced walls from Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Spacer.

Vanilla Weapons Expanded is part of a series of mods expanding on everyday life on the Rimworld. When paired together with a brand new Vanilla Apparel Expanded and Vanilla Armours Expanded, you can bring something to your game that will keep you interested in it for days.</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/AndroidQuazar/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>