<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VBE_HotCoffeeHigh.label>hot coffee high</VBE_HotCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_HotCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in one's nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 15% amount and 15% reduction in rest fall rate. Hot coffee reduces hypothermia, cold reduces heatstroke.</VBE_HotCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_HotCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>a coffee high</VBE_HotCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>

  <VBE_IcedCoffeeHigh.label>iced coffee high</VBE_IcedCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_IcedCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 15% amount and 15% reduction in rest fall rate. Hot coffee reduces hypothermia, cold reduces heatstroke.</VBE_IcedCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_IcedCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>a coffee high</VBE_IcedCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>


  <!-- Caffeine Addiction -->

  <VBE_CaffeineTolerance.label>caffeine tolerance</VBE_CaffeineTolerance.label>
  <VBE_CaffeineTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to caffeine. The more severe this tolerance is, the more caffeine it takes to get the same effect.</VBE_CaffeineTolerance.description>

  <VBE_CaffeineAddiction.label>caffeine addiction</VBE_CaffeineAddiction.label>
  <VBE_CaffeineAddiction.description>A chemical addiction to caffeine. Long-term presence of caffeine has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.
\nWithout regular doses of caffeine, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</VBE_CaffeineAddiction.description>
  <VBE_CaffeineAddiction.stages.1.label>withdrawal</VBE_CaffeineAddiction.stages.1.label>


</LanguageData>