<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: The Shattered Empire, once a symbol of tyranny and oppression, has crumbled. All over the planet, brave deserters rose in a chorus of rebellion, breaking the chains of servitude that held them bound. Every child who now wakes to the dawn of freedom will remember and revere these names, the names of the heroes who dared to challenge the impossible:\n{0}\nHowever, this is not the end, but merely a transition. With the old empire now but ruins and their flagship a burning wreckage fallen from the skies, a time for healing and rebuilding is upon us. The nobles, once loyal to the empire, now surrender to outlander communities or lose themselves in a life of crime. There's no denying the truth - the world has forever changed.\nAs you stand at the threshold of a new era, you remember this chapter of defiance and courage. The echoes of the Shattered Empire will serve as a reminder of your resilience, a testament to your unfaltering quest for freedom. You look ahead, knowing that you are stepping into a future built on hope, unity, and liberation. -->
  <VFED.EndgameText>Раздробленная империя, некогда являвшаяся символом тирании и угнетения, пала. По всей планете в едином порыве восстали отважные дезертиры, разорвав сковывающие их цепи рабства. Каждый ребёнок, который сейчас встречает рассвет свободы, будет помнить и чтить имена героев, осмелившихся бросить вызов невозможному:\n{0}\nОднако это не конец, а лишь переходный период. От старой империи остались лишь руины, а её флагман превратился в горящие обломки, и теперь наступает время исцеления и восстановления. Представители знати, некогда верные Империи, переходят на сторону общин чужеземцев или оказываются втянутыми в преступную жизнь. Нельзя отрицать одного — мир изменился навсегда.\nСтоя на пороге новой эры, вы помните эту главу смелости и сопротивления. Отголоски Раздробленной империи будут служить напоминанием о вашей стойкости и несгибаемом стремлении к свободе. Вы смотрите вперёд, зная, что вас ждёт будущее, построенное на надежде, единстве и освобождении.</VFED.EndgameText>
  <!-- EN: You are about to initiate a final mission in Vanilla Factions Expanded: Deserters. After the mission is complete, the Empire and the Deserters will be no more. Are you sure you want to initiate the final mission? -->
  <VFED.EndgameWarningText>Вы приступаете к выполнению финальной миссии мода Vanilla Factions Expanded: Deserters. После её завершения Империя и Дезертиры перестанут существовать. Вы уверены, что хотите начать финальную миссию?</VFED.EndgameWarningText>
</LanguageData>