<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VCE_CannedMeat.label>canned meat</VCE_CannedMeat.label>
  <VCE_CannedMeat.description>Meat vacuum sealed and secured in a steel can effectively extending shelf life indefinitely. While edible cold right out of the can it's far more nourishing mixed into a meal and heated.\n\nCanned goods are intended as a way to preserve food and use it an an ingredient later, not as a final meal.</VCE_CannedMeat.description>

  <VCE_CannedProduce.label>canned produce</VCE_CannedProduce.label>
  <VCE_CannedProduce.description>Produce vacuum sealed and secured in a steel can effectively extending shelf life indefinitely. While edible cold right out of the can it's far more nourishing mixed into a meal and heated.\n\nCanned goods are intended as a way to preserve food and use it an an ingredient later, not as a final meal.</VCE_CannedProduce.description>

  <VCE_CannedFruit.label>canned fruit</VCE_CannedFruit.label>
  <VCE_CannedFruit.description>Cooked and preserved fruit in a hermetically sealed, durable container. Preserved food lasts indefinitely without refrigeration.\n\nFruit differs from produce in that it is specifically required in the production of desserts.\n\nCanned goods are intended as a way to preserve food and use it an an ingredient later, not as a final meal.</VCE_CannedFruit.description>

  <VCE_CannedAP.label>canned eggs</VCE_CannedAP.label>
  <VCE_CannedAP.description>Boiled eggs vacuum sealed and secured in a steel can effectively extending shelf life indefinitely. While edible cold right out of the can it's far more nourishing mixed into a meal and heated.\n\nCanned goods are intended as a way to preserve food and use it an an ingredient later, not as a final meal.</VCE_CannedAP.description>

  <VCE_CannedFish.label>canned fish</VCE_CannedFish.label>
  <VCE_CannedFish.description>Fish vacuum sealed and secured in a steel can effectively extending shelf life indefinitely. While edible cold right out of the can it's far more nourishing mixed into a meal and heated.\n\nCanned goods are intended as a way to preserve food and use it an an ingredient later, not as a final meal.</VCE_CannedFish.description>


</LanguageData>