<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Hippopotamus -->

  <AEXP_Leather_Hippopotamus.label>hippopotamus leather</AEXP_Leather_Hippopotamus.label>
  <AEXP_Leather_Hippopotamus.description>A thick leather of a hippopotamus. Not only it's extremely durable, but it also provides considerable heat insulation.</AEXP_Leather_Hippopotamus.description>


  <!-- Wildebeest -->

  <AEXP_Leather_Wildebeest.label>wildebeest pelt</AEXP_Leather_Wildebeest.label>
  <AEXP_Leather_Wildebeest.description>A thick but crumbly wildebeest fur and leather. Whilst it provides some degree of damage protection, the overall longevity of the item decreases.</AEXP_Leather_Wildebeest.description>


  <!-- Platypus leather -->

  <AEXP_Leather_Platypus.label>platypus leather</AEXP_Leather_Platypus.label>
  <AEXP_Leather_Platypus.description>Platypus fur was considered a valuable commodity in the days of old Terra, a fact that almost drove the Platypus to extinction. Luckily, the animal was protected and thrived again.</AEXP_Leather_Platypus.description>


  <!-- Lion -->

  <AEXP_Leather_Lion.label>lion pelt</AEXP_Leather_Lion.label>
  <AEXP_Leather_Lion.description>A strong, luxurious leather of the leader of the animal kingdom. Often sought after by urbworld philanthropists.</AEXP_Leather_Lion.description>


  <!-- Camel -->

  <WoolCamel.label>camel wool</WoolCamel.label>
  <WoolCamel.description>Camel's wool. It provides good insulation from heat.</WoolCamel.description>


  <!-- Pinnipeds -->

  <AEXP_Leather_Pinniped.label>pinniped leather</AEXP_Leather_Pinniped.label>
  <AEXP_Leather_Pinniped.description>Tanned and dried leather from a Pinniped. It is of average strength but insulates well against heat.</AEXP_Leather_Pinniped.description>


  <!-- Tiger leather -->

  <AEXP_Leather_Tiger.label>tiger leather</AEXP_Leather_Tiger.label>
  <AEXP_Leather_Tiger.description>Tigers were often the target of poachers in old Earth due to their luxurious pelts, a fact that almost drove them to extinction. With the near lawlessness of the Rim, tiger leather is seen as another exotic commodity to trade between settlements.</AEXP_Leather_Tiger.description>


  <!-- Musk Ox -->

  <AEXP_MuskOxWool.label>musk ox wool</AEXP_MuskOxWool.label>
  <AEXP_MuskOxWool.description>The inner wool of the muskox, originally known in Inuktitut as Qiviuq. Stronger and warmer than sheep's wool, and softer than cashmere wool.</AEXP_MuskOxWool.description>


</LanguageData>