<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EN: archon -->
	<VRE_Archon.label>archon</VRE_Archon.label>
  <!-- EN: A complete mystery whose earliest recorded appearance has been tied to the development of archotechnology and the first occurrences of Transcendence, the archons are an enigmatic race of quasi-humans capable of moving between dimensions. They have an optimized physiology for psycasting and are renowned for extreme levels of aggression even amongst themselves.\n\nDue to lack of communication between humans and archons, very little concrete information has been gleaned from what few interactions have been documented amongst the stars. However, there are numerous instances of archons kidnapping humans throughout the entirety of known space and any attempts at killing them are thwarted by the dimensional rifts from which they appear. No current technology exists that can observe, much less cross, different dimensions, and yet these archons appear without warning, following no pattern, and always exploiting any vulnerabilities. Their equipment appears to be of archotech origin, aligning with reports of planets with a significant human presence undergoing Transcendence, exhibiting a correspondingly elevated presence of archons. -->
	<VRE_Archon.description>A complete mystery whose earliest recorded appearance has been tied to the development of archotechnology and the first occurrences of Transcendence, the archons are an enigmatic race of quasi-humans capable of moving between dimensions. They have an optimized physiology for psycasting and are renowned for extreme levels of aggression even amongst themselves.\n\nDue to lack of communication between humans and archons, very little concrete information has been gleaned from what few interactions have been documented amongst the stars. However, there are numerous instances of archons kidnapping humans throughout the entirety of known space and any attempts at killing them are thwarted by the dimensional rifts from which they appear. No current technology exists that can observe, much less cross, different dimensions, and yet these archons appear without warning, following no pattern, and always exploiting any vulnerabilities. Their equipment appears to be of archotech origin, aligning with reports of planets with a significant human presence undergoing Transcendence, exhibiting a correspondingly elevated presence of archons.</VRE_Archon.description>



</LanguageData>