<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>





  <!-- Animal Stats -->

  <VAERoy_PrimaryRole>Primary Role</VAERoy_PrimaryRole>
  <VAERoy_SecondaryRole>Secondary Role</VAERoy_SecondaryRole>

  <!-- Roles -->

  <VAERoy_Combat>Combat</VAERoy_Combat>
  <VAERoy_EggLayer>Egg Layer</VAERoy_EggLayer>

  <VAERoy_Utility>Utility</VAERoy_Utility>
  <VAERoy_UtilityMood>Utility - Mood</VAERoy_UtilityMood>
  <VAERoy_UtilitySocial>Utility - Social</VAERoy_UtilitySocial>
  <VAERoy_UtilityHeat>Utility - Heat Disipation</VAERoy_UtilityHeat>
  <VAERoy_UtilityPsychic>Utility - Psychic</VAERoy_UtilityPsychic>
  <VAERoy_UtilityCrowd>Utility - Crowd Control</VAERoy_UtilityCrowd>
  <VAERoy_UtilityFood>Utility - Food</VAERoy_UtilityFood>
  <VAERoy_UtilityBuilding>Utility - Building</VAERoy_UtilityBuilding>

  <!-- Roles Descriptions -->

  <VAERoy_CombatDescInc>Combat animals are specialized in melee combat. These animals have high attack damage, good resistance, high health, or other abilities that allow them to survive in the front lines.\n\nThis animal gets greatly increased melee attacks as it ages.</VAERoy_CombatDescInc>
  <VAERoy_CombatDesc>Combat animals are specialized in melee combat. These animals have high attack damage, good resistance, high health, or other abilities that allow them to survive in the front lines.</VAERoy_CombatDesc>
  <VAERoy_EggLayerDesc>This animal lays eggs</VAERoy_EggLayerDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilityMoodDesc>This animal is not suited for combat, being quite physically weak. It will however increase the mood of your colonists.</VAERoy_UtilityMoodDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilityHeatDisipationDesc>This animal is not suited for combat, being quite physically weak. It will however increase the neural heat disipation of a bonded colonist.</VAERoy_UtilityHeatDisipationDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilitySocialDesc>This animal is not suited for combat. It will instead engage your colonists in conversation, increasing their social recreation as well as giving them small amounts of experience in random skills.</VAERoy_UtilitySocialDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilityPsychicDesc>This animal is not suited for combat, being quite physically weak. It will however nuzzle your colonists periodically to increase their psychic sensitivity.</VAERoy_UtilityPsychicDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilityCrowdDesc>This animal is weak, but it has psychic abilities that can help with crowd control and survivavility.</VAERoy_UtilityCrowdDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilityFoodDesc>This is a farm animal that produces specialized meat.</VAERoy_UtilityFoodDesc>
  <VAERoy_UtilityBuildingDesc>This animal is not suited for combat, being quite physically weak. It will however build nests that act as a very beautiful animal sleeping spot.</VAERoy_UtilityBuildingDesc>
















</LanguageData>