<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- EN: strigoi -->
	<VRE_Strigoi.label>strigoi</VRE_Strigoi.label>
	<!-- EN: The Strigoi were born out of a catastrophic experiment gone awry. A brilliant scientist sought to create the ultimate soldier by merging the DNA of humans and a now-extinct bat-like creature known as the Desmodus. In pursuit of immortality and power, scientist infused these hybrid beings with archites, rendering them deathless and ageless. The Strigoi possess a terrifying visage, with features reminiscent of both humans and bats. Their bodies are covered in a layer of viscous fluid that enhances their ability to heal from any injury, rendering them immune to disease and poison. In battle, the Strigoi are formidable opponents, using their massive talons to tear their enemies apart with ruthless efficiency.\n\nOver the millennia, the Strigoi have been both feared and hunted for their unnatural abilities and the threat they pose to the balance of power in the universe. They have been forced to live in the shadows, hiding from those who would destroy them, yet ever seeking to expand their influence and further their own mysterious agenda.\n\nSome believe that the Strigoi are nothing more than myths and legends, while others whisper of secret cabals of Strigoi controlling entire civilizations from behind the scenes. There are tales of Strigoi orchestrating brutal blood feuds in the darkest corners of the distant planets, or lurking within the shadows of massive space stations, manipulating events to suit their inscrutable purposes. -->
	<VRE_Strigoi.description>The Strigoi were born out of a catastrophic experiment gone awry. A brilliant scientist sought to create the ultimate soldier by merging the DNA of humans and a now-extinct bat-like creature known as the Desmodus. In pursuit of immortality and power, scientist infused these hybrid beings with archites, rendering them deathless and ageless. The Strigoi possess a terrifying visage, with features reminiscent of both humans and bats. Their bodies are covered in a layer of viscous fluid that enhances their ability to heal from any injury, rendering them immune to disease and poison. In battle, the Strigoi are formidable opponents, using their massive talons to tear their enemies apart with ruthless efficiency.\n\nOver the millennia, the Strigoi have been both feared and hunted for their unnatural abilities and the threat they pose to the balance of power in the universe. They have been forced to live in the shadows, hiding from those who would destroy them, yet ever seeking to expand their influence and further their own mysterious agenda.\n\nSome believe that the Strigoi are nothing more than myths and legends, while others whisper of secret cabals of Strigoi controlling entire civilizations from behind the scenes. There are tales of Strigoi orchestrating brutal blood feuds in the darkest corners of the distant planets, or lurking within the shadows of massive space stations, manipulating events to suit their inscrutable purposes.</VRE_Strigoi.description>
	<!-- EN: Strigoi are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are viscous and resemble a half-human half-bat hybrid. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. In combat, they use their huge talons to rip their prey to pieces. The price is that strigoi sanguophages must consume hemogen derived from either human blood or animal blood to survive, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They lose their hemogen supply quickly due to high entropy, and need to replenish it regularly to sustain themselves. They're easily destroyed by fire, and suffer extreme penalties in UV light. -->
	<VRE_Strigoi.descriptionShort>Strigoi are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are viscous and resemble a half-human half-bat hybrid. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. In combat, they use their huge talons to rip their prey to pieces. The price is that strigoi sanguophages must consume hemogen derived from either human blood or animal blood to survive, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They lose their hemogen supply quickly due to high entropy, and need to replenish it regularly to sustain themselves. They're easily destroyed by fire, and suffer extreme penalties in UV light.</VRE_Strigoi.descriptionShort>
	
	<!-- EN: ekkimian -->
	<VRE_Ekkimian.label>ekkimian</VRE_Ekkimian.label>
	<!-- EN: In the darkest reaches of the universe, the Ekkimian vampires were birthed from the twisted ambitions of a rogue scientist named Dr. Mortis. Obsessed with the concept of death and resurrection, Dr. Mortis sought to create a new breed of immortals by fusing archites with the DNA of humans and a mysterious, long-extinct species that thrived on consuming the dead. The Ekkimian vampires, as they came to be known, are grotesque and horrifying in appearance. Resembling desiccated corpses more than living beings, their monstrous visages instill terror in all who lay eyes upon them. Despite their hideous appearance, the Ekkimian vampires possess incredible regenerative abilities, healing any injury and remaining immune to disease and poison.\n\nEkkimian vampires must consume hemogen derived exclusively from human corpses to survive. This morbid requirement has led them to lurk in the shadows, scavenging the remains of fallen warriors and feeding on the aftermath of battles. Like other sanguophages, they must periodically enter deathrest to recover their strength and replenish their hemogen reserves.\n\nThere are whispered tales of entire planets falling under the sway of Ekkimian vampire lords, who feed on the corpses of their enemies and rule with an iron, undead fist. Fearful of the day when these monstrous beings might rise up and unleash their full power, the inhabitants of the colonized planets must remain ever vigilant, lest they become mere fodder for the insatiable hunger of the Ekkimians. -->
	<VRE_Ekkimian.description>In the darkest reaches of the universe, the Ekkimian vampires were birthed from the twisted ambitions of a rogue scientist named Dr. Mortis. Obsessed with the concept of death and resurrection, Dr. Mortis sought to create a new breed of immortals by fusing archites with the DNA of humans and a mysterious, long-extinct species that thrived on consuming the dead. The Ekkimian vampires, as they came to be known, are grotesque and horrifying in appearance. Resembling desiccated corpses more than living beings, their monstrous visages instill terror in all who lay eyes upon them. Despite their hideous appearance, the Ekkimian vampires possess incredible regenerative abilities, healing any injury and remaining immune to disease and poison.\n\nEkkimian vampires must consume hemogen derived exclusively from human corpses to survive. This morbid requirement has led them to lurk in the shadows, scavenging the remains of fallen warriors and feeding on the aftermath of battles. Like other sanguophages, they must periodically enter deathrest to recover their strength and replenish their hemogen reserves.\n\nThere are whispered tales of entire planets falling under the sway of Ekkimian vampire lords, who feed on the corpses of their enemies and rule with an iron, undead fist. Fearful of the day when these monstrous beings might rise up and unleash their full power, the inhabitants of the colonized planets must remain ever vigilant, lest they become mere fodder for the insatiable hunger of the Ekkimians.</VRE_Ekkimian.description>
	<!-- EN: Ekkimian are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are extremely ugly and resemble dessicated corpses more than humans. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. In combat, they can excrete toxic clouds around themselves, and rapidly regenerate any wounds at the cost of hemogen. The price is that ekkimian sanguophages must consume hemogen derived from human corpses and only corpses, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They're easily destroyed by fire, and slowed down by UV light. -->
	<VRE_Ekkimian.descriptionShort>Ekkimian are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are extremely ugly and resemble dessicated corpses more than humans. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. In combat, they can excrete toxic clouds around themselves, and rapidly regenerate any wounds at the cost of hemogen. The price is that ekkimian sanguophages must consume hemogen derived from human corpses and only corpses, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They're easily destroyed by fire, and slowed down by UV light.</VRE_Ekkimian.descriptionShort>
	
	<!-- EN: bruxa -->
	<VRE_Bruxa.label>bruxa</VRE_Bruxa.label>
	<!-- EN: In the complex tapestry of the universe, the Bruxas emerged as a unique and alluring subxenotype of sanguophage. Created by an enigmatic archotech entity seeking to weave together beauty and power, the Bruxas were gifted with unparalleled grace and charm. Designed as the ultimate companions to other sanguophages, the Bruxas were engineered with the unique ability to bond with their brethren and feed on their blood, bestowing mutual benefits upon both parties.\n\nThe Bruxas are ageless and deathless, their bodies imbued with archotech-created archites that grant them extraordinary abilities. Possessing an ethereal beauty, they are irresistibly captivating to those who cross their paths. In addition to their regenerative powers, which allow them to heal any injury and remain immune to disease and poison, Bruxas have the remarkable ability to filter infections from the bloodstream of other humans, purifying their blood and filling them with an overwhelming sense of ecstasy in the process.\n\nThroughout the ages, the Bruxas have been both feared and revered for their beguiling beauty and potent abilities. Often serving as confidants and companions to powerful individuals, including sanguophage lords, they have been known to wield considerable influence in the shadow societies. Their unique ability to bond with other humans has led to the formation of secret alliances and networks, further solidifying their power and influence.\n\nIn the vast expanse of the universe, the Bruxas remain an enigma - seductive and mysterious, their true intentions hidden behind a veil of allure and grace. Those who encounter a Bruxa must tread carefully, for while their touch may bring unimaginable pleasure, it may also lead to a fate more treacherous than one could ever imagine. -->
	<VRE_Bruxa.description>In the complex tapestry of the universe, the Bruxas emerged as a unique and alluring subxenotype of sanguophage. Created by an enigmatic archotech entity seeking to weave together beauty and power, the Bruxas were gifted with unparalleled grace and charm. Designed as the ultimate companions to other sanguophages, the Bruxas were engineered with the unique ability to bond with their brethren and feed on their blood, bestowing mutual benefits upon both parties.\n\nThe Bruxas are ageless and deathless, their bodies imbued with archotech-created archites that grant them extraordinary abilities. Possessing an ethereal beauty, they are irresistibly captivating to those who cross their paths. In addition to their regenerative powers, which allow them to heal any injury and remain immune to disease and poison, Bruxas have the remarkable ability to filter infections from the bloodstream of other humans, purifying their blood and filling them with an overwhelming sense of ecstasy in the process.\n\nThroughout the ages, the Bruxas have been both feared and revered for their beguiling beauty and potent abilities. Often serving as confidants and companions to powerful individuals, including sanguophage lords, they have been known to wield considerable influence in the shadow societies. Their unique ability to bond with other humans has led to the formation of secret alliances and networks, further solidifying their power and influence.\n\nIn the vast expanse of the universe, the Bruxas remain an enigma - seductive and mysterious, their true intentions hidden behind a veil of allure and grace. Those who encounter a Bruxa must tread carefully, for while their touch may bring unimaginable pleasure, it may also lead to a fate more treacherous than one could ever imagine.</VRE_Bruxa.description>
	<!-- EN: Bruxas are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are extremely beautiful, and almost always bond with other sanguophages. Unlike other subxenotypes of that species, bruxas are capable of feeding on sanguophage blood, providing them with great benefits. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. They can filter infection out of the bloodstream of other humans, as well as fill them with a sense of strong ecstasy. The price is that bruxa must sometimes consume hemogen - either human or sanguophage, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They're easily destroyed by fire, and slowed down by UV light. -->
	<VRE_Bruxa.descriptionShort>Bruxas are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are extremely beautiful, and almost always bond with other sanguophages. Unlike other subxenotypes of that species, bruxas are capable of feeding on sanguophage blood, providing them with great benefits. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. They can filter infection out of the bloodstream of other humans, as well as fill them with a sense of strong ecstasy. The price is that bruxa must sometimes consume hemogen - either human or sanguophage, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They're easily destroyed by fire, and slowed down by UV light.</VRE_Bruxa.descriptionShort>
</LanguageData>