<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: questName->Techprinter demolition -->
  <VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <li>questName->налёт на центр печати чертежей</li>
  </VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <!-- EN: questDescription->We have received the news of a techprinter installation belonging to [empire_name] near our location. Techprinters are a huge environmental hazard, and are used by techfriars to replicate their knowledge on techprints.\nTechite discs used in this process are extremely toxic and flammable. We might be able to ignite a stack of these discs and see the inferno unfold.\nThe techprinter installation is protected by:\n[forces_description].\nTwo palintone turrets are located at the installation. They are powerful, anti-infantry weapons firing large-caliber shells at incredible speeds, dealing heavy damage over significant ranges. Their ammo needs to be stored right next to them, and a precise shot might set off a chain explosion.\nWe have also been informed that the location is protected by a number of ground-mounted striker turrets. Despite the limited range, these turrets can easily reveal our approach and provide covering fire for the imperial army.\nTwo techfriars are most certainly at the installation. Killing them is not necessary.\nThe techprinter installation is protected by a number of surveillance pillars. They should not be approached, and instead should be disabled from afar - either by destroying them, or cutting off their power. Once activated, they will greatly increase our visibility.\nThe objective of this assignment is to destroy the techprinters by any means necessary. Once that is done, the reward will arrive and we will have to make our escape.\nOnce we arrive at the installation, we can expect an imperial response if our visibility is high enough. We will only have a limited amount of time to complete the mission.
 -->
  <VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
  <li>questDescription->Мы узнали, что неподалёку от нас находится центр печати чертежей, принадлежащий [empire_name]. Находящиеся там техитовые принтеры представляют чрезвычайную опасность для окружающей среды. Имперские техномонахи используют их для передачи и сохранения своих знаний в виде специальных чертежей.\nИспользуемые в процессе печати техитовые диски очень токсичны и огнеопасны. Возможно, мы сможем поджечь стопку таких дисков и издали понаблюдать за тем, как разверзнется ад.\nЦентр печати защищают:\n[forces_description]\nНам сообщили о присутствии двух турелей класса «Палинтон». Это мощные противопехотные орудия стреляют крупнокалиберными снарядами с огромной скорострельностью, нанося серьёзный урон на значительном расстоянии. Неподалёку от турелей расположены необходимые для перезарядки ящики с тяжёлыми снарядами. Эти ящики взывоопасны и точный выстрел спровоцирует детонацию.\nКроме этого, на территории будут размещены ударные турели. Несмотря на ограниченную дальнобойность, они могут легко обнаружить нас и обеспечить огневое прикрытие имперских сил.\nВ комлексе, скорее всего, находятся два техномонаха. Убивать их не обязательно.\nЦентр печати охраняется мачтами слежения. Не рекомендуется подходить к ним, так как их активация существенно увеличит осведомлённость Империи о наших действиях. Лучше отключить их с расстояния, разрушив или обесточив.\nЦель миссии — уничтожить техитовые принтеры любым доступным способом. Как только это будет сделано, будет отправлена награда и нам придётся немедленно покинуть местность.\nЕсли уровень заметности нашей фракции высок, мы должны быть готовы к реакции Империи. Время выполнения задания ограничено.</li>
  </VFED_TechprinterDemolition.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
</LanguageData>
