<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Radio_Industrial.label>industrial radio</Radio_Industrial.label>
  <Radio_Industrial.description>An old device from a bygone era, it is able to pick up radio waves and play them back. Even on the rimworlds, there is often an old transmitter or lone radio station broadcasting something.</Radio_Industrial.description>

  <Radio_Spacer.label>longwave radio</Radio_Spacer.label>
  <Radio_Spacer.description>A high tech radio reciever that is able to pick up very faint signals and play them back at crystal clear quality.</Radio_Spacer.description>

  <Joy_Arcade.label>arcade machine</Joy_Arcade.label>
  <Joy_Arcade.description>A tall cabinet that holds a small cathode ray display and control panel for playing a variety of pre-installed games.</Joy_Arcade.description>

  <Joy_InudstrialComputer.label>old computer</Joy_InudstrialComputer.label>
  <Joy_InudstrialComputer.description>A desktop computer based off an old design, very inefficient and prone to crashing. Gives a minor boost to learning after use.</Joy_InudstrialComputer.description>

  <Joy_ModernComputer.label>modern computer</Joy_ModernComputer.label>
  <Joy_ModernComputer.description>A high tech computer with utilising an LCD monitor and better performance parts that are less prone to crashing. Gives a boost to learning after use.</Joy_ModernComputer.description>

  <Joy_Piano.label>piano</Joy_Piano.label>
  <Joy_Piano.description>A large playable piano for practising on, quite enjoyable and it is a great way to develop artistic talent.</Joy_Piano.description>

  <Joy_RouletteTable.label>roulette table</Joy_RouletteTable.label>
  <Joy_RouletteTable.description>A soft-topped bounded table with a wheel for playing roulette, a good way to train your social skills and luck.</Joy_RouletteTable.description>

  <Joy_DartsBoard.label>darts board</Joy_DartsBoard.label>
  <Joy_DartsBoard.description>A popular game among rimworlds involving throwing darts at a circular target, It's relaxing, and trains shooting skills at a higher rate than horseshoes or hoopstone.</Joy_DartsBoard.description>

  <Joy_PunchingBag.label>punching bag</Joy_PunchingBag.label>
  <Joy_PunchingBag.description>A fabric filled punching bag to let out anger on. Can be quite calming and helps to train melee ability.</Joy_PunchingBag.description>


</LanguageData>