<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Settlers</name>
  <author>Oskar Potocki, LimeTreeSnake, Kikohi</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.SettlersModule</packageId>
  <description>After the success of our Vanilla Factions Expanded - Medieval, which was a faction mod closing the gap between tribal faction and outlander faction, we have begun work on another faction mod - this time adding frontier settlers, inspired by western films. The scope of this mod is quite similar to our Medieval mod, so you can expect it to be a well fitting mini-expansion.

Thanks to Vanilla Factions Expanded - Settlers, you can experience the harsh reality of being a gang of bandits on the rimworld frontier. Settlements of this faction are built in the same way they were in frontier America - with a main road separating a town into two parts. Thanks to new outfits and headgear, as well as several new weapons, your colonists will be able to blend in perfectly alongside all those thugs and prospectors shooting each other on the streets and drinking chemshine - a new, highly volatile chemfuel distilled alcohol. A large amount of new chemfuel-themed structures allow you to witness the power of combustible fuel, making your bases look just like the wild west settlements! A new starting scenario allows you to play bandits, a faction hostile to every other civilisation on the planet, and with new world quests you can become a bounty hunter or a caravan raider! Sorry, no stagecoach robbery included!

A new storyteller, Diego Dire, would like to tell you a story that begins with the blaze of glory. Not only will he provide you with more western-style events than regular, vanilla events, he will also scale backwards - meaning the beginning will be difficult, but it will slowly become more and more friendly. That is, of course, until Diego decides to start the cycle all over again, throwing the worst of the worst at you. Can you handle the challenge?

With a native support for the other Vanilla Expanded mods, settlers will come equipped with Vanilla Apparel Expanded clothing, whilst thanks to Vanilla Weapons Expanded, bandits will start using lever action rifles and sawed-off shotguns!

And watch out for drunk muffalos. Those beasts love chemshine!
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>