<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VPE_Flameball.label>flameball</VPE_Flameball.label>
  <VPE_Flameball.description>Generate a small fragile pod of magma as the caster lobs the projectile away. Upon impact, the liquid bursts forth in a small radius.</VPE_Flameball.description>

  <VPE_SelfExplosion.label>self explosion</VPE_SelfExplosion.label>
  <VPE_SelfExplosion.description>Creates a brief-lived incendiary vortex skipgate around the caster that is connected to hidden reservoirs of pressurized flammable gas. As the gas escapes, it ignites and spreads rapidly, dealing little direct damage but will set almost everything it touches on fire.</VPE_SelfExplosion.description>

  <VPE_Explosion.label>explosion</VPE_Explosion.label>
  <VPE_Explosion.description>Generates a brief, micro skipgate within underground reservoirs of unrefined organic chemicals, along with a tiny spark at the designated location. Burning gas bursts forth in a large radius and elements of chemfuel spurt out uncontrollably.</VPE_Explosion.description>

  <VPE_FireShield.label>fire shield</VPE_FireShield.label>
  <VPE_FireShield.description>Creates a temporary incendiary vortex skipgate around a target that links to a nearby star that extends outward by a few inches. Anyone that attempts to attack the target in melee will be set ablaze, with the additional benefit of overpowering any other fire effects.</VPE_FireShield.description>

  <VPE_BreatheFlame.label>breathe flame</VPE_BreatheFlame.label>
  <VPE_BreatheFlame.description>Generates a brief, unidirectional skipgate within underground reservoirs of unrefined organic chemicals, along with a tiny spark in front of the caster’s mouth. Jets of blazing, unrefined chemfuel streak forth setting everything on fire.</VPE_BreatheFlame.description>

  <VPE_EyeBlast.label>eye blast</VPE_EyeBlast.label>
  <VPE_EyeBlast.description>Generates two micro, unidirectional skipgates in front of the caster’s eyes which link to a nearby white dwarf. Targeting a location to prevent overshooting, the blinding energy shoots forth and sets a small area ablaze.</VPE_EyeBlast.description>

  <VPE_QuenchFlames.label>extinguish flames</VPE_QuenchFlames.label>
  <VPE_QuenchFlames.description>Generates skipgates linked to passing nearby ships that “misplaces” the firefoam contained in the ship’s fire suppression system. As there is a lot to “borrow”, the radius is quite impressive.</VPE_QuenchFlames.description>

  <VPE_MeteorShower.label>meteor shower</VPE_MeteorShower.label>
  <VPE_MeteorShower.description>Introduces gravitational distortions in orbiting meteoroids and space debris to strike a location of the caster’s choosing. These come in groups of 4 to ensure optimal control and devastation.</VPE_MeteorShower.description>

  <VPE_FireBeam.label>fire beam</VPE_FireBeam.label>
  <VPE_FireBeam.description>Attempts to recreate the power of a star inside a concentrated column of almost liquidized oxygen. The resulting emission of plasma is so powerful that only the most advanced weapons systems can hope to compare.</VPE_FireBeam.description>

  <VPE_FlameTornado.label>fire tornado</VPE_FlameTornado.label>
  <VPE_FlameTornado.description>Attempts to recreate the power of a star inside a vortex of concentrated oxygen. The mess of reactions occurring creates flammable byproducts in its wake while also leaving its trajectory completely unpredictable.</VPE_FlameTornado.description>


</LanguageData>