<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VPE_Bolt.label>bolt</VPE_Bolt.label>
  <VPE_Bolt.description>Hurls a weak bolt of electricity to strike a small target, inflicting minor burns on direct hits and area EMP damage.</VPE_Bolt.description>

  <VPE_ChainBolt.label>chain bolt</VPE_ChainBolt.label>
  <VPE_ChainBolt.description>Projects a living bolt of electricity to a target which can then follow up with 5 more nearby targets, inflicting small burns and EMP damage.</VPE_ChainBolt.description>

  <VPE_Thunderbolt.label>thunderbolt</VPE_Thunderbolt.label>
  <VPE_Thunderbolt.description>Summons a bolt of lightning to strike a target, inflicting burns on direct hits and a larger area EMP damage.</VPE_Thunderbolt.description>

  <VPE_StaticAura.label>static aura</VPE_StaticAura.label>
  <VPE_StaticAura.description>The caster designates a nearby target to receive an aura of surging electricity, which will inflict EMP effects on anything foreign that they approach, including structures, pawns and electrical objects.</VPE_StaticAura.description>

  <VPE_Recharge.label>recharge</VPE_Recharge.label>
  <VPE_Recharge.description>Carefully and delicately tunes a stream of electricity to a touched battery to charge it with 100kW or the equivalent of 100 Wd/s. The duration of charge depends on the caster’s psychic sensitivity.</VPE_Recharge.description>

  <VPE_BallLightning.label>ball lightning</VPE_BallLightning.label>
  <VPE_BallLightning.description>The caster compresses a ball of condensed electricity which will slowly move to a designated location. A few seconds after release, it will start discharging into nearby surrounding targets with living bolts of electricity.</VPE_BallLightning.description>

  <VPE_StaticPulse.label>static pulse</VPE_StaticPulse.label>
  <VPE_StaticPulse.description>The caster dumps a massive amount of voltage into the surrounding air, causing an EMP blast in a huge radius which is otherwise harmless.</VPE_StaticPulse.description>

  <VPE_Vortex.label>vortex</VPE_Vortex.label>
  <VPE_Vortex.description>Manifests a gaping vortex of high-voltage electricity - redirected via skipgate from a nebula storm - at a target area with a large effect. Severely hampers movement and manipulating proportionately, with the strongest effect at the center.</VPE_Vortex.description>

  <VPE_Hurricane.label>hurricane</VPE_Hurricane.label>
  <VPE_Hurricane.description>The caster forcibly changes the weather - using widespread differential-pressure skipgates - to a downpour with hurricane-force winds, which lasts as long as the caster can manage the heat accumulation and can instantly stop at-will. Those outdoors will experience progressively severe limitations to sight, moving and manipulation to the point they come to a complete stop.</VPE_Hurricane.description>

  <VPE_Flashstorm.label>flashstorm</VPE_Flashstorm.label>
  <VPE_Flashstorm.description>Use concentrated differential-pressure skipgates in the atmosphere to generate a localized flashstorm. The storm will strike the area with lightning for some time before dissipating.</VPE_Flashstorm.description>


</LanguageData>