<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VPE_EnchantQuality.label>enchant quality</VPE_EnchantQuality.label>
  <VPE_EnchantQuality.description>The caster concentrates on an item and attempts to improve its quality by reshaping the material slightly, but cannot imitate a master’s handiwork.</VPE_EnchantQuality.description>

  <VPE_Mend.label>mend</VPE_Mend.label>
  <VPE_Mend.description>The caster concentrates on an item and attempts to repair present damage by rebinding the material, with the effect scaling with their psychic sensitivity.</VPE_Mend.description>

  <VPE_ConjureHeatPearls.label>conure heat pearls</VPE_ConjureHeatPearls.label>
  <VPE_ConjureHeatPearls.description>Converts a minimum amount of the caster’s heat into metaphysical pearls. These can be thrown at other psycasters to induce massive amounts of heat on them, but are otherwise harmless.</VPE_ConjureHeatPearls.description>

  <VPE_Haywire.label>haywire</VPE_Haywire.label>
  <VPE_Haywire.description>Designates an area to experience psychic interference, effectively scrambling electronic systems’ IFFs while identifying the caster’s people as allies. Duration scales with psychic sensitivity.</VPE_Haywire.description>

  <VPE_Power.label>power</VPE_Power.label>
  <VPE_Power.description>Metaphysically alters the designated equipment’s power input to extract energy directly from fluctuations in the quantum foam for a few days. Duration scales with psychic sensitivity.</VPE_Power.description>

  <VPE_RockConstruct.label>rock construct</VPE_RockConstruct.label>
  <VPE_RockConstruct.description>Converts a minimum amount of the caster’s heat capacity into metaphysical crystals to be implanted into a stone chunk. This new rock construct is capable of performing simple chores, and breaking the crystal allows the heat capacity to be restored.</VPE_RockConstruct.description>

  <VPE_SteelConstruct.label>steel construct</VPE_SteelConstruct.label>
  <VPE_SteelConstruct.description>Converts a minimum amount of the caster’s heat capacity into metaphysical crystals to be implanted into a steel slag. This new steel construct will follow the caster and defend them from harm, and breaking the crystal allows the heat capacity to be restored.</VPE_SteelConstruct.description>

  <VPE_CraftPsyRing.label>craft psyring</VPE_CraftPsyRing.label>
  <VPE_CraftPsyRing.description>Psychically alters the form of a piece of eltex into the shape of a ring, which is imbued with psycasting knowledge of the caster. When worn by another psycaster, this temporarily allows them to use this knowledge to perform the stored psycast without practice.</VPE_CraftPsyRing.description>

  <VPE_WordofProgress.label>word of progress</VPE_WordofProgress.label>
  <VPE_WordofProgress.description>Speak words encouraging problem solving capabilities while psychically hypercharging the target’s mind with keen insight. The target will experience double research speed and intellectual skill gain for 5 days, scaling with their psychic sensitivity.</VPE_WordofProgress.description>

  <VPE_ReverseEngineer.label>reverse engineer</VPE_ReverseEngineer.label>
  <VPE_ReverseEngineer.description>The caster concentrates on an object and attempts to unravel the knowledge needed to manufacture more of them. The long, intense concentration ends with the caster falling into a 6-hour coma.</VPE_ReverseEngineer.description>


</LanguageData>