<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Modded -->

  <VWE_ThumpRetrofit.label>thump retrofit</VWE_ThumpRetrofit.label>
  <VWE_ThumpRetrofit.description>This weapon incorporates reverse-engineered mechanoid technology to fire heavy, blunt-force energy slugs that devastate structures and armor at the cost of range.</VWE_ThumpRetrofit.description>

  <VWE_AcidInjectorFlechettes.label>acid-injector flechettes</VWE_AcidInjectorFlechettes.label>
  <VWE_AcidInjectorFlechettes.description>This weapon has been re-barreled to fire fin-stabilized acid-injector flechettes. These rounds cause horrific internal dissolution in organic targets but are useless against mechanoids.</VWE_AcidInjectorFlechettes.description>

  <VWE_DeserterMarkings.label>deserter markings</VWE_DeserterMarkings.label>
  <VWE_DeserterMarkings.description>This weapon bears defaced Imperial crests; equipping it in the presence of Imperial caravans or visitors will be recognized as treason, causing an immediate and severe drop in relations.</VWE_DeserterMarkings.description>

  <VWE_HighAngleDraw.label>high-angle draw</VWE_HighAngleDraw.label>
  <VWE_HighAngleDraw.description>This weapon is strung for extreme parabolic arcing, allowing arrows to be lobbed over walls and obstacles to hit unseen targets, though it is impossible to aim precisely.</VWE_HighAngleDraw.description>

  <VWE_LuckyShots.label>lucky shots</VWE_LuckyShots.label>
  <VWE_LuckyShots.description>This weapon's action is tuned for occasional moments of perfect alignment, granting a chance for shots to bypass defenses and inflict significant bonus damage.</VWE_LuckyShots.description>

  <VWE_MakeshiftTrait.label>makeshift</VWE_MakeshiftTrait.label>
  <VWE_MakeshiftTrait.description>This weapon is cobbled together from mismatched parts with a faulty sear mechanism. It is wildly unpredictable; sometimes it fails to fire entirely, while other times it accidentally discharges a double-length burst.</VWE_MakeshiftTrait.description>

  <VWE_AncientTrait.label>ancient</VWE_AncientTrait.label>
  <VWE_AncientTrait.description>This weapon is a relic from a bygone era, its internal stress fractures held together by mere luck. It functions normally for a limited time, but after a set number of shots, the mechanism will shatter completely and the weapon will be destroyed.</VWE_AncientTrait.description>

  <VWE_CryptoRounds.label>crypto rounds</VWE_CryptoRounds.label>
  <VWE_CryptoRounds.description>This weapon fires rounds coated in active cryptoparticles that induce a rapid stasis-freeze effect on impact.</VWE_CryptoRounds.description>

  <VWE_VoidInscriptions.label>void inscriptions</VWE_VoidInscriptions.label>
  <VWE_VoidInscriptions.description>This weapon is etched with shifting, non-euclidean glyphs that whisper to the wielder, continually draining their mental stability while equipped.</VWE_VoidInscriptions.description>


</LanguageData>