<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Universal -->

  <VWE_SkeletonizedFrame.label>skeletonized frame</VWE_SkeletonizedFrame.label>
  <VWE_SkeletonizedFrame.description>This weapon has had non-essential metal drilled out to drastically reduce weight. It increases the user's movement speed, but the structural integrity is compromised, lowering the weapon's maximum durability.</VWE_SkeletonizedFrame.description>

  <VWE_WeightedStock.label>weighted stock</VWE_WeightedStock.label>
  <VWE_WeightedStock.description>This weapon features a reinforced, heavy stock designed for bludgeoning. It significantly increases melee damage and stun chance, but the added weight increases aiming time.</VWE_WeightedStock.description>

  <VWE_PortedBarrel.label>ported barrel</VWE_PortedBarrel.label>
  <VWE_PortedBarrel.description>This weapon has gas vents drilled near the muzzle to counteract recoil. It reduces the cooldown time between shots, allowing for faster sustained fire, but slightly reduces maximum range.</VWE_PortedBarrel.description>

  <VWE_IlluminatedSights.label>illuminated sights</VWE_IlluminatedSights.label>
  <VWE_IlluminatedSights.description>This weapon is fitted with self-illuminating sights. It provides a consistent accuracy increase across all ranges, particularly useful in poor lighting conditions.</VWE_IlluminatedSights.description>

  <VWE_MatchTrigger.label>match trigger</VWE_MatchTrigger.label>
  <VWE_MatchTrigger.description>This weapon features a finely tuned, sensitive trigger mechanism. It improves accuracy at medium and long ranges, but requires a deliberate, gentle squeeze, which slightly increases aiming time.</VWE_MatchTrigger.description>

  <VWE_FireSelector.label>fire selector</VWE_FireSelector.label>
  <VWE_FireSelector.description>This weapon has been modified to fire controlled, semi-automatic shots rather than fully automatic sprays. It fires fewer shots per burst, but gains a massive accuracy boost at medium and long ranges.</VWE_FireSelector.description>

  <VWE_Akimbo.label>akimbo</VWE_Akimbo.label>
  <VWE_Akimbo.description>This weapon is paired with a matching duplicate, allowing the colonist to dual-wield. It doubles the number of rounds fired in a burst and doubles the fire rate, but aiming two weapons simultaneously significantly reduces accuracy.</VWE_Akimbo.description>


</LanguageData>